<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-08-09T00:41:27.869Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-08-09T00:41:27.869Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Update Statement – Update Query in SQL]]></title>
        <id>61067c973306a507d1bfc1ba</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-update-statement-update-query-in-sql/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T21:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once you have created a table in a database, it will rarely need to stay the same forever. You will likely need to modify the records in it.  And to help you do that, there is a useful statement, aptly named UPDATE, that you can use to change the records]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Row VS Column in Excel – What is the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>610cebc13306a507d1bfeca9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/row-vs-column-in-excel-what-is-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T21:17:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Excel displays data in tabular format. This means that information is arranged in a table consisting of rows and columns.  Rows and columns are different properties that together make up a table.  These are the two most important features of Excel that allow users to store and manipulate their]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SVG Gobbler]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346259</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svg-gobbler/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T19:32:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Great little project from Ross Moody: 
SVG Gobbler is a browser extension that finds the vector content on the page you’re viewing and gives you the option to download, optimize, copy, view the code, or export it as an image.
…
The post SVG Gobbler appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insert Into SQL – SQL Insert Statement Example]]></title>
        <id>6107c0593306a507d1bfc565</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/insert-into-sql-sql-insert-statement-example/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T16:10:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've created an empty table in your database you'll need to add records to it. In this article you will learn how you can add records to your tables using the INSERT statement in SQL. Keep in mind that if the syntax presented here doesn't work, you can check]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Switch Case – JS Switch Statement Example]]></title>
        <id>610658bf3306a507d1bfc110</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-switch-case-js-switch-statement-example/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T15:18:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are times in JavaScript where you might consider using a switch statement instead of an if else statement.   switch statements can have a cleaner syntax over complicated if else statements.  Take a look at the example below – instead of using this long if else statement, you might choose to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Efficient Infinite Utility Helpers Using Inline CSS Custom Properties and calc()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345467</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/efficient-infinite-utility-helpers-using-inline-css-custom-properties-and-calc/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T14:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently wrote a very basic Sass loop that outputs several padding and margin utility classes. Nothing fancy, really, just a Sass map with 11 spacing values, looped over to create classes for both padding and margin on each side. …
The post Efficient Infinite Utility Helpers Using Inline CSS Custom Properties and calc() appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Ford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gridless.design]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345878</id>
        <link href="https://gridless.design/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T14:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donnie D’Amato built a whole site around the thesis that “digital designers still expect to use the grid while experienced layout engineers have moved beyond it.” The idea isn’t that we should never literally use display: grid; but rather that …
The post gridless.design appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Useful VSCode Extensions For Web Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/useful-vscode-extensions-web-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/useful-vscode-extensions-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code can be supercharged wuth hundreds of [VS Code extensions](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/). In this article, Leonardo shares four useful extensions that help him in his daily work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[&lt;pre&gt; Tag in HTML – Example Code]]></title>
        <id>610be0ea3306a507d1bfe4b1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pre-tag-in-html-example-code/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T21:33:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HTML <pre> tag defines a preformatted block of text. It comes in handy when you want to display text where the typographical formatting affects the meaning of the content, such as code snippets and poems.  By default, browsers ignore white space of any kind – extra text space,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Security – How to Use Dynamic Admission Control to Secure Your Container Supply Chain]]></title>
        <id>6108233d3306a507d1bfc731</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kubernetes-security-dynamic-admission-control/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T16:37:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers have exploded in popularity in recent years. And as more developers are using these containers, they need more tools to manage them and their interactions with them effectively.  To help manage all this, many devs use Kubernetes. And it has become the de facto standard for container orchestration. While]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Buggy React Code Examples and How to Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345418</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/three-buggy-react-code-examples-and-how-to-fix-them/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T14:24:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s usually more than one way to code a thing in React. And while it’s possible to create the same thing different ways, there may be one or two approaches that technically work “better” than others. I actually run into …
The post Three Buggy React Code Examples and How to Fix Them appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hugh Haworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>60db390127f80207bcdbb455</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-crash-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T14:19:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML is used to create web pages.  This article will teach you the basics of HTML. I also created a 45-minute video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that teaches you HTML in the context of creating an actual web page. If you are just learning HTML, I recommend]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Disabled Buttons]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/frustrating-design-patterns-disabled-buttons/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/frustrating-design-patterns-disabled-buttons/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can we make disabled buttons more inclusive? When do they work well, and when do they fail on us? And finally, when do we actually need them, and how can we avoid them? Let’s find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Full-Stack Mobile Application With Flutter, Fauna, and GraphQL]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345552</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-build-a-full-stack-mobile-application-with-flutter-fauna-and-graphql/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T09:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
Flutter is Google’s UI framework used to create flexible, expressive cross-platform mobile applications. It is one of the fastest-growing frameworks for mobile app development. On the other hand, Fauna is a transactional, developer-friendly serverless …
The post How to Build a Full-Stack Mobile Application With Flutter, Fauna, and GraphQL appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shadid Haque</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State Of Web Workers In 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345866</id>
        <link href="https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-workers-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T23:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You gotta appreciate the tenacity of Surma. He’s been advocating for Web Workers as a path forward to better-feeling websites for a lot of years now. He’s at it again making sure we all understand the landscape:
[…] regardless 
…
The post The State Of Web Workers In 2021 appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Border – Style and HTML Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>610afe863306a507d1bfdf1e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-border-style-and-html-code-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T23:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In CSS, everything is a box. And each box – whether it's text, an image, a div, a span, or any other element – has a border that separates its edges from other boxes around it.  The CSS border property allows us to do several things with the border of individual boxes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Padding – CSS Padding Order]]></title>
        <id>6106575b3306a507d1bfc104</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-padding-css-padding-order/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T21:33:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we are going to learn about CSS padding properties, the shorthand property, and how padding differs from margin.  What is padding in CSS?CSS padding creates space around the element's content. This space is within the element's border and margin.  Let's take a look at the CSS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Where – Clause Examples]]></title>
        <id>6106638c3306a507d1bfc15c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-where-clause-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T15:32:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes when you're working with SQL, you don't need to operate on an entire range of records. Or it would be really bad if you accidentally changed or deleted everything. In these cases, you'll need to select only the part of the records on which you want to work, those]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using CSS Shapes for Interesting User Controls and Navigation]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345274</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-css-shapes-for-interesting-user-controls-and-navigation/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T14:13:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Straight across or down, that’s the proverbial order for user controls on a screen. Like a list of menu items. But what if we change that to a more fluid layout with bends, curves, and nooks? We can pull it …
The post Using CSS Shapes for Interesting User Controls and Navigation appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Children And Iteration Methods]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/react-children-iteration-methods/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/react-children-iteration-methods/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll discuss and learn about the use case of iterating over React `children` and the ways to do it. In particular, we will deep dive into one of the utility methods, `React.Children.toArray`, that React gives us, which helps to iterate over the children in a way which ensures performance and determinism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Arihant Verma)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless Functions as Proxies]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345744</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/serverless-functions-as-proxies/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T20:23:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first time cloud functions / serverless functions clicked for me was when I saw and tried Auth0’s (now defunct) Webtask. It was a little CodePen-like IDE but you didn’t really see anything aside from code and logs. The …
The post Serverless Functions as Proxies appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatic Daily GitHub Backups, Restored in Seconds]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345807</id>
        <link href="https://srv.buysellads.com/ads/long/x/TCZHURZTTTTTTT3IJZ7NTTTTTTTVINFLKTTTTTTTADBXPYTTTTTTTIDNVJR6YWS22M4647ZVKMPW454EQMNWVWPMPABT"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T20:22:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
Any company that uses GitHub for critical applications needs a backup that can be restored quickly when needed. Cyberattacks, human errors, or a forced push are just some of the scenarios that can result …
The post Automatic Daily GitHub Backups, Restored in Seconds appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rewind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep Dive on Skipping to Content]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345154</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-deep-dive-on-skipping-to-content/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T14:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While most people browsing the web on a computer use a mouse, many rely on their keyboard instead. Theoretically, using a web page with the keyboard should not be a problem — press the TAB key to move the keyboard …
The post A Deep Dive on Skipping to Content appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Ratcliffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build Resilient JavaScript UIs]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/build-resilient-javascript-ui/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/build-resilient-javascript-ui/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Resilience is intrinsic to the web and therefore us, web developers. This article explores how graceful degradation, defensive coding, observability, and a healthy attitude towards failures better equips us before, during, and after an error occurs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Callum Hart)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Modules (The Native Ones)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345756</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-modules-the-native-ones/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T18:28:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They are actually called “CSS Module Scripts” and are a native browser feature, as opposed to the popular open-source project that essentially does scoped styles by creating unique class name identifiers in both HTML and CSS. 
Native CSS Modules are …
The post CSS Modules (The Native Ones) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Code a Playable Synth Keyboard]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345178</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-code-a-playable-synth-keyboard/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T14:36:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a little knowledge of music theory, we can use regular HTML, CSS and JavaScript — without any libraries or audio samples — to create a simple digital instrument. Let’s put that into practice and explore one method for creating …
The post How to Code a Playable Synth Keyboard appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bret Cameron</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring CSS: Strategy, Regression Testing And Maintenance (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/refactoring-css-strategy-regression-testing-maintenance-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/refactoring-css-strategy-regression-testing-maintenance-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll take a deep dive into the refactoring process itself, and cover incremental refactoring strategy, visual regression testing, and maintaining the refactored codebase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Vibes In August (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New month, new wallpapers! In this post, you’ll find unique and inspiring wallpapers for August 2021. Created with love by the community for the community, they come in versions with and without a calendar for the month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Shared ESLint Configuration]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345628</id>
        <link href="https://katydecorah.com/code/eslint-config/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T20:07:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looks like it was almost 9 years ago when Airbnb first published their JavaScript Style Guide. 112k stars on GitHub later, it seems like the de facto preset for Babel / ES Lint. But it’s not the only company …
The post A Shared ESLint Configuration appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conjuring Generative Blobs With The CSS Paint API]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345256</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/conjuring-generative-blobs-with-the-css-paint-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T14:54:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Paint API (part of the magical Houdini family) opens the door to an exciting new world of design in CSS. Using the Paint API, we can create custom shapes, intricate patterns, and beautiful animations — all with a …
The post Conjuring Generative Blobs With The CSS Paint API appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Francis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An E-Commerce Site With Angular 11, Commerce Layer And Paypal]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/ecommerce-angular11-headless-paypal/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/ecommerce-angular11-headless-paypal/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having an e-commerce store is crucial for any store owner as more and more customers are turning to online shopping. In this tutorial, we shall go through how to create an e-commerce site with Angular 11. The site will use the Commerce Layer as a headless e-commerce API and use Paypal to process payments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Explains the Open Graph Images]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345518</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-06-22-framework-building-open-graph-images/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T19:49:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An explanation of those new GitHub social media images:
[…] our custom Open Graph image service is a little Node.js app that uses the GitHub GraphQL API to collect data, generates some HTML from a template, and pipes it to 
…
The post GitHub Explains the Open Graph Images appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Is No Such Thing As A CSS Absolute Unit]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/css-absolute-units/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/css-absolute-units/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are absolute units? What are the differences between relative and absolute units, and how do we create accurate sizes on the web? In this article, Elad Shechter explains why CSS absolute units aren’t so absolute.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Elad Shechter)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating An Accessible Dialog From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/accessible-dialog-from-scratch/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/accessible-dialog-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dialogs are everywhere in modern interface design (for good or for bad), and yet many of them are not accessible to assistive technologies. In this article, we will dig into how to create a short script to create accessible dialogs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kitty Giraudel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global vs. Local Styling In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/global-local-styling-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/global-local-styling-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js has strong opinions about how to organize JavaScript but not CSS. How can we develop patterns that encourage best CSS practices while also following the framework’s logic? The answer is surprisingly simple — to write well-structured CSS that balances global and local styling concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alexander Dubovoy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Serverless Functions And The International Space Station]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/gatsby-serverless-functions-international-space-station/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/gatsby-serverless-functions-international-space-station/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby recently announced the launch of “functions”. In this article, Paul Scanlon explains how to get the current location of the International Space Station (ISS) as it orbits the Earth in real-time using [Gatsby Functions](https://www.gatsbyjs.com/docs/reference/functions/) and then display it on a 3D interactive globe using [React Three Fibre](https://github.com/pmndrs/react-three-fiber).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Attracting Clients To Your Agency]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/guide-attracting-clients-agency/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/guide-attracting-clients-agency/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many web design agencies consider it a badge of honor that they win work exclusively through word-of-mouth recommendations. In this article, Paul Boag explains why that is entirely the wrong attitude and what to do about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Time To Your Schedule As A Professional]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/time-schedule-professional-trafft/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/time-schedule-professional-trafft/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you running a business and have too many things going on at once? Meetings, bugs, customer feedback, new clients in addition to your already tight deadlines? Let’s face it, time management is hard, and it becomes even more difficult in the trying times we are in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthew Talebi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Color Tools And Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/color-tools-resources/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/color-tools-resources/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? We’ve collected some useful color tools and resources that we’ve discovered lately — to help you get the most out of your creativity. We’ve also just recently covered [CSS auditing tools](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-auditing-tools/), [CSS generators](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-generators/), [accessible front-end components](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/complete-guide-accessible-front-end-components/), [front-end boilerplates](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/) and [VS code extensions](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/) — you might find them useful, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Migrate From WordPress To A Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/wordpress-headless-cms-storyblok/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/wordpress-headless-cms-storyblok/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will look at when it makes sense to migrate from a monolithic project to a headless setup and the benefits that come with it. In addition to a step-by-step guide on how to migrate WordPress to Storyblok Headless CMS, the problems that will arise during the process and how to deal with them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alba Silvente)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maintaining End-To-End Quality With Visual Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/maintaining-end-to-end-quality-visual-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/maintaining-end-to-end-quality-visual-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By adding visual elements to your tests, you can gain more options to add meaningful ways in maintaining a high level of quality for your app. Colby Fayock explains how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Colby Fayock)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Insights I Gained While Researching Vue.js Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/three-insights-vuejs-accessibility/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/three-insights-vuejs-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web app accessibility appears difficult because it seems that there is little information on the subject available online. Let’s take a closer look at the accessible use of framework features, concrete Vue.js traits, as well as community initiatives and vetted patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcus Herrmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ISR vs DPR: Big Words, Quick Explanation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/isr-dpr-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/isr-dpr-explained/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two strategies for incrementally building websites that are growing in popularity: Incremental Static Regeneration and Distributed Persistent Rendering. What’s the difference? Let’s figure it out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cassidy Williams)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Do That With A JavaScript Data Grid?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/javascript-data-grid-kendo-ui/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/javascript-data-grid-kendo-ui/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you’ll get to see some pretty groundbreaking things you can achieve with modern JavaScript grids and discover new ways to augment a data grid to make it engaging, responsive, and accessible. All this will be illustrated using Kendo UI Data Grids and their features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Broken Filters]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frustrating-design-patterns-broken-frozen-filters/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frustrating-design-patterns-broken-frozen-filters/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Too often dealing with filters can be frustrating. Let’s get them right. That means never freeze the UI on a single input, provide text input fallback and never auto-scroll users on a single input. Here’s why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Dynamic Header With Intersection Observer]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/dynamic-header-intersection-observer/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/dynamic-header-intersection-observer/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, attaching an event listener to constantly fire a callback on scroll can be performance-intensive. But there is a better way with Intersection Observer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Migrate From jQuery To Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/migrate-jquery-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/migrate-jquery-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’re taking a closer look at different approaches and strategies on how we can migrate a web application that uses jQuery framework, and start using one of the coolest React frameworks in the market: Next.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring CSS: Introduction (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/refactoring-css-introduction-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/refactoring-css-introduction-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS refactoring is not an easy task — it needs to be done in a way that doesn't create problems. First we need to analyze the existing codebase, audit CSS codebase health, discover weaknesses, agree on the approach, and convince management to invest time and resources into the process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>