<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-09-21T00:42:52.087Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-09-21T00:42:52.087Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resources aren’t requested by CSS, but by the DOM]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352089</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/resources-arent-requested-by-css-but-by-the-dom/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T23:16:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a good tweet from Harry:
Simple yet significant thing all developers should keep in mind: CSS resources (fonts, background images) are not requested by your CSS, but by the DOM node that needs them [Note: slight oversimplification, but 
…
The post Resources aren’t requested by CSS, but by the DOM appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up reCAPTCHA v3 in a Laravel Project]]></title>
        <id>5fbf192a49c47664ed825d46</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-setup-recaptcha-v3-in-laravel/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T22:26:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll learn how to set up reCAPTCHA v3 in your Laravel project. This can be a bit tricky, so I'll help you simplify the process here.  What is reCaptcha?reCaptcha is a Google service provided for free that helps you protect your websites from spam and malicious]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Tuple VS List – What is the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>61483e50852f4307d3730d48</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-tuple-vs-list-what-is-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T21:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tuples and lists are two of the four available built-in data types that you can use to store data in Python.  They are both useful and they might seem similar at first glance. But they have significant differences and each one is best used in different cases.  This article will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use react-icons to install Font Awesome in a React app]]></title>
        <id>61330a1fd6679a07b7d41e3e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-icons/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T19:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React-icons is a small library that helps you add icons (from all different icon libraries) to your React apps. It delivers the icons to your app as components so they're easier to work with, and it lets you style them so they're consistent with the overall style of your app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot Tutorial – How to Build Fast and Modern Java Apps]]></title>
        <id>613a5047852f4307d372a9ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/spring-boot-tutorial-build-fast-modern-java-app/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T19:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I am going to walk you through building a prototype with Spring Boot. Think of it like building a project for a hackathon or a prototype for your startup in limited time.  In other words, we are not trying to build something perfect – but rather something that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embracing Asymmetrical Design]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352274</id>
        <link href="https://www.bennadel.com/blog/4102-embracing-asymmetrical-design-and-overcoming-the-harmful-effects-of-text-overflow-ellipsis-in-css.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T19:17:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ll never forget one of Karen McGrane’s great lessons to the world: truncation is not a content strategy. The idea is that just clipping off text programmatically is a sledgehammer, and avoids the kind of real thinking and planning that …
The post Embracing Asymmetrical Design appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[imba]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352283</id>
        <link href="https://imba.io/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T19:13:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not every day you see a new processor for building websites that reinvents the syntax for HTML and CSS and JavaScript. That’s what imba is doing.
That’s an awful lot of vendor lock-in, but I guess if you get …
The post imba appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Django for Everybody - Learn the Popular Python Framework from Dr. Chuck]]></title>
        <id>6148d0dc9456b407b870f5ba</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/django-for-everybody-learn-the-popular-python-framework-from-dr-chuck/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T18:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Django is one of the most popular ways to create full-stack websites with Python. We just published an 18-hour Django course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Charles Severance (a.k.a. Dr. Chuck) created this course, along with the popular Python for Everybody course. He is a Clinical Professor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the CSS Paint API: Polygon Border]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=351917</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/exploring-the-css-paint-api-polygon-border/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T14:36:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nowadays, creating complex shapes is an easy task using clip-path, but adding a border to the shapes is always a pain. There is no robust CSS solution and we always need to produce specific “hacky” code for each particular …
The post Exploring the CSS Paint API: Polygon Border appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ascending Order with SQL Order By]]></title>
        <id>612cbfd8b5177808226d4a47</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ascending-order-with-sql-order-by/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T14:29:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will show you a few code examples on how you can sort your data in ascending order using the ORDER BY clause in SQL.  ORDER BY syntaxThis is the basic syntax to sort your data in ascending order: SELECT columns FROM table ORDER BY column;If]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Contraction? Grammar and Definition]]></title>
        <id>614382b2852f4307d372f2d6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-contraction-grammar-and-definition/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T13:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take  a look at the following sentences:  I’m learning how to  code.  I'll get a software developer job.  Learning how to code doesn’t have to cost you money.  The words I’m, I’ll and doesn’t are called contractions.  In this article, you'll learn all about contractions]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Imposter Domains Re-Publishing Your Website?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/imposter-domains-republishing-website/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/imposter-domains-republishing-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content scraping is a fact of life on the Internet. When you think of web scraping, you probably do not think about the scrapers turning around and immediately serving your entire, whole page content on another website. But what if your site content is being re-published?  It might be already happening.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ken Harker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Beautiful Shadows in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352082</id>
        <link href="https://www.joshwcomeau.com/css/designing-shadows/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T22:49:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My favorite kind of blog post is when someone takes a subject that I’ve spent all of five minutes considering and then says—no!—this is an enormous topic worthy of a dissertation. Look at all the things you can do with …
The post Designing Beautiful Shadows in CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Rendle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSV Format – How to Open a .csv File and Export it]]></title>
        <id>613f3cc7852f4307d372c7e4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/csv-format-how-to-open-a-csv-file-and-export-it/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T18:22:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might have heard of a CSV file but what does it mean?  In this article, we are going to learn what a CSV file is, and how to open and export them using Microsoft Excel and Google Sheets.  What is a CSV file? CSV stands for Comma Separated Values.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computer Science Unleashed, Chapter 1: Connections]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=350843</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/computer-science-unleashed-chapter-1-connections/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T15:27:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humans crave connections, and the advent of the digital revolution has empowered us to be more connected than ever before. The Internet has unleashed upon billions of people unprecedented economic and political freedom, as well as powerful means of control and domination. Yet, the vast majority of us are oblivious to its inner workings.
The post Computer Science Unleashed, Chapter 1: Connections appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wladston Viana Ferreira Filho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monetize Open-Source Software With Gatsby Functions And Stripe]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/monetize-open-source-software-gatsby-functions-stripe/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/monetize-open-source-software-gatsby-functions-stripe/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Functions provide front-end developers a way to write and use server-side code without the hassle of maintaining a server. If making money from open-source is of interest to you and your site isn’t built using Gatsby, this approach may well be the answer you were looking for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Start Freelancing – Tips for Launching a Successful Freelance Career]]></title>
        <id>613f6bc9852f4307d372ca83</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-start-freelancing/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T22:25:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Freelancing can be an incredibly rewarding way to make money online. But it can also be quite difficult if you don't approach it in the right way.  It takes more than a stable internet connection to make a living as a freelancer. In order to make the big bucks, you’]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shadow Roots and Inheritance]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=351915</id>
        <link href="https://kittygiraudel.com/2021/08/23/shadow-roots-and-inheritance/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T20:14:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a helluva gotcha with styling a <details> element, as documented here by Kitty Guiraudel. It’s obscure enough that you might never run into it, but if you do, I could see it being very confusing (it would confuse …
The post Shadow Roots and Inheritance appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REST API Best Practices – REST Endpoint Design Examples]]></title>
        <id>614353d8852f4307d372ef7e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rest-api-best-practices-rest-endpoint-design-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T17:50:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Web Development, REST APIs play an important role in ensuring smooth communication between the client and the server.  You can think of the client as the front end and the server as the back end.  Communication between the client (frontend) and the server (backend) isn't usually super direct. So]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minding the “gap”]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=351481</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/minding-the-gap/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T14:34:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might already know about the CSS gap property. It isn’t exactly new, but it did gain an important new ability last year: it now works in Flexbox in addition to CSS Grid. That, and the fact that I …
The post Minding the “gap” appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Brosset</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Static Site Generators vs. CMS-powered Websites: How to Keep Marketers and Devs Happy]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=351586</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/static-site-generators-vs-cms-powered-websites-how-to-keep-marketers-and-devs-happy/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T14:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
Many developers love working with static site generators like Gatsby and Hugo. These powerful yet flexible systems help create beautiful websites using familiar tools like Markdown and React. Nearly every popular modern programming …
The post Static Site Generators vs. CMS-powered Websites: How to Keep Marketers and Devs Happy appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philip Kiely</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Quality Assurance: From User Requirements To Web Risk Management]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/journey-into-web-quality-assurance/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/journey-into-web-quality-assurance/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twenty years ago, Elie Sloïm chose to dedicate his professional life to web quality assurance. He started asking, ”What does quality mean for a web user?” Well, this article explains everything he has learned along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Elie Sloïm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reasons To Build A CRM-Powered Website For Your Business]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reasons-build-crm-powered-website-business/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reasons-build-crm-powered-website-business/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating a CRM with your business website has numerous benefits. In this article, Zara Cooper explains what these benefits are and why websites should be integrated with a CRM platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.1"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T06:39:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Unexpected nested element in author field crashes the parser
Thank you @ad-m]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2021 Scroll Survey Report]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=351987</id>
        <link href="https://web.dev/2021-scroll-survey-report/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T22:39:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s a common thought and question: how do browsers prioritize what they work on? We get little glimpses of it sometimes. We’re told to “star issues” in bug trackers to signal interest. We’re told to get involved in GitHub threads …
The post 2021 Scroll Survey Report appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[kbar]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=351868</id>
        <link href="https://kbar.vercel.app/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T18:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not every day that a new pattern emerges across the web, but I think cmd + k is here to stay.  It’s a keyboard shortcut that usually pops open a search UI and it lets you toggle settings on …
The post kbar appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Rendle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Intro to JavaScript Proxy]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=351767</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/an-intro-to-javascript-proxy/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T14:21:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever been in a situation where you wish you could have some control over the values in an object or array? Maybe you wanted to prevent certain types of data or even validate the data before storing it …
The post An Intro to JavaScript Proxy appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Travis Almand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing The Need For Pseudo-Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reducing-need-pseudo-elements/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reducing-need-pseudo-elements/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, pseudo-elements have faithfully helped front-end developers implement creative designs. While they still have an important place, we can now leave pseudo-elements behind in some scenarios, thanks to newer CSS properties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcel Moreau)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the `dl`]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=351518</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/on-the-dl/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T22:37:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blogging about HTML elements¹? *chefs kiss*
Here’s Ben Myers on the (aptly described) “underrated” Definition List (<dl>) element in HTML:
You might have also seen lists of name–value pairs to describe lodging amenities, or to list 
…
The post On the `dl` appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Form in PHP Using DOMDocument]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=351454</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/building-a-form-in-php-using-domdocument/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T14:36:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to build an HTML form in PHP using DOMDocument — a structured and expressive way to build logical markup.
The post Building a Form in PHP Using DOMDocument appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Land</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jamstack Conf 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=351970</id>
        <link href="https://jamstackconf.com/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T14:32:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
What? Jamstack Conf! It’s the best! Learn what’s happening and what’s next for this hot ecosystem.
When? October 6–7, 2021
Where? Virtual / online.
How much? It’s free! There are workshops as well though, …
The post Jamstack Conf 2021 appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Power Of Pen And Paper Sketching]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/power-pen-paper-sketching/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/power-pen-paper-sketching/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing for digital spaces, it’s natural to default to digital mockup tools, but doing so cuts out a world of possibilities. Analog drawing can unleash your imagination and allow you to focus on what’s most important at the start: the ideas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tracy Osborn)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orchestrating Complexity With Web Animations API]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/orchestrating-complexity-web-animations-api/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/orchestrating-complexity-web-animations-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are way too many options in Web Animations API to pick them up that easily. Learning how timing works and how to control the playback of several animations at once makes for a solid foundation on which to base your projects on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kirill Myshkin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: Excellent Editorial]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-design-done-well-excellent-editorial/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-design-done-well-excellent-editorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They say content is king, and they’re right. The web has unlocked untold possibilities for storytellers — provided the story is right, of course. Here are some of our favorite examples of editorial content thriving in the digital realm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using SWR React Hooks With Next.js’ Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/useswr-react-hook-library-incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/useswr-react-hook-library-incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When paired with ISR and Next.js’ API routes, SWR can be used to create a responsive user experience. In this article, Sam Poder explains what SWR is, where to use it (and where not), and how to build a website by using Incremental Static Regeneration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sam Poder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Decisions For Building Flexible Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/developer-decisions-building-flexible-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/developer-decisions-building-flexible-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll walk through the process of taking a seemingly simple design for a text-and-media component and deciding how best to translate it into code, keeping in mind the needs of both users and content authors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Smashing Online Workshops on Front-End & UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/new-smashing-online-workshops-sep-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/new-smashing-online-workshops-sep-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the state of HTML Email, Vue.js and Next.js? What are new, smart interface design patterns we could use? Let’s figure it out. With our brand new online workshops on front-end & design. Now with **free workshops** for you to test the waters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New With DevTools: Cross-Browser Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/devtools-cross-browser-edition/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/devtools-cross-browser-edition/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what’s new with developer tools in Firefox, Edge, Chrome and Safari. Discover new and powerful features that will help you be more comfortable and productive when testing and debugging across browsers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Patrick Brosset)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP/3: Practical Deployment Options (Part 3)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/http3-practical-deployment-options-part3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/http3-practical-deployment-options-part3/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After almost five years in development, the new HTTP/3 protocol is nearing its final form. Let’s take a close look at the challenges involved in deploying and testing HTTP/3, and how and if you should change your websites and resources as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Robin Marx)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing Carbon Emissions On The Web]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reducing-carbon-emissions-on-web/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reducing-carbon-emissions-on-web/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-03T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Websites, unfortunately, aren’t as environmentally friendly as we might like them to be. This article contains some thoughts and experiences from trying to clean them up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Berwyn Powell)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive Learning Tools For Front-End Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/interactive-learning-tools-front-end-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/interactive-learning-tools-front-end-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive coding tools to help you learn CSS, JavaScript, SQL, React, Vim, regular expressions and Jamstack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep Dive Into The Wonderful World Of SVG Displacement Filtering]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/deep-dive-wonderful-world-svg-displacement-filtering/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/deep-dive-wonderful-world-svg-displacement-filtering/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What exactly is a displacement filter? In this article, Dirk Weber explains the SVG `feDisplacementMap` filter primitive with a good number of examples to demonstrate the concept of animated displacement maps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dirk Weber)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State Management In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/state-management-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/state-management-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-31T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By combining some React APIs, we can accurately manage “simple” states. With Next.js though, we can quickly find situations where we need to accommodate many other requirements. Let’s have a look at some patterns to accomplish all that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stories Of September (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-september-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-september-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New month, new wallpapers! In this post, you’ll find inspiring wallpaper designs for September 2021. They were created with love by artists and designers from across the globe and are available with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring CSS: Optimizing Size And Performance (Part 3)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/refactoring-css-optimizing-size-performance-part3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/refactoring-css-optimizing-size-performance-part3/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-30T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many CSS optimization techniques to tackle potential file size and performance issues. Let’s take a look at some of them. After all, if deploying the refactored codebase causes loading or performance issues, it will result in less traffic and revenue, which might leave the management and project managers dissatisfied.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compound Components In React]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/compound-components-react/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/compound-components-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compound components help developers build more expressive and flexible APIs to share state and logic within components. This tutorial explains how this can be achieved with the help of using the Context API and React to build components by using this advanced pattern.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ichoku Chinonso)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pushing Back Against Privacy Infringement On The Web]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/against-privacy-infringement-web/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/against-privacy-infringement-web/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-26T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Web is still wrestling with issues we take for granted offline, privacy chief among them. These are steps The New York Times took to protect users’ data, and how you can too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Robin Berjon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A Public/Private Multi-Monorepo For PHP Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/public-private-multi-monorepo-php-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/public-private-multi-monorepo-php-projects/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-25T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Leonardo explains how to use a "multi-monorepo" approach for making the development experience faster, yet keeping your PHP packages private. This solution can be especially beneficial for PRO plugin creators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Automate Documentation Workflow For Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/automate-documentation-workflow-for-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/automate-documentation-workflow-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you’ll learn how to save hours of tedious work of writing, updating, and correcting technical documentation. In this article, you will learn how to automate your documentation workflow with Vale and GitHub Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Portia Burton)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP/3: Performance Improvements (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/http3-performance-improvements-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/http3-performance-improvements-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-23T06:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After almost five years in development, the new HTTP/3 protocol is nearing its final form. Let’s take a close look at the performance improvements of HTTP/3, congestion control, head-of-line-blocking, and 0-RTT connection set-up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Robin Marx)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>