<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-11-03T00:41:26.047Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-11-03T00:41:26.047Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proxying Third-Party JavaScript as First-Party JavaScript (and the Potential Effect on Analytics)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354619</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/proxying-third-party-javascript-as-first-party-javascript-and-the-potential-effect-on-analytics/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T22:50:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First, check out how incredibly easy it is to write a Cloudflare Worker to proxy another URL:
addEventListener("fetch", (event) ={
  event.respondWith(
     fetch("https://css-tricks.com")
  );
});
It doesn’t have any error handling or anything, but hey, it works:
Now imagine how …
The post Proxying Third-Party JavaScript as First-Party JavaScript (and the Potential Effect on Analytics) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GUI Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=355016</id>
        <link href="https://web.dev/shows/gui-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T21:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I keep bookmarking Adam’s GUI Challenges posts/videos and, before I even have a chance to review and link them up, another one is already published! Fortunately, the homepage for them on web.dev is a nice roundup. 
For example, a recent …
The post GUI Challenges appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Bonjour on my Computer? Windows 10 Bonjour Program PC Guide]]></title>
        <id>617fffad8bcfae07ca4df6d2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-bonjour-on-my-computer/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T18:23:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple devices work well and connect readily with other Apple devices. But they have a hard time communicating with devices running other operating systems like Windows and Linux.  If you have both Apple and Windows devices, you might want to share files between them over a local network. And this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change Mouse DPI Settings in Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>61810f888bcfae07ca4e007b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-change-mouse-dpi-settings-in-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T17:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If your work requires a lot of precision, like graphic design and gaming, then you might want to adjust how fast or slow your external mouse or keyboard is.  In this guide, I will show you how you can make your mouse more sensitive or less sensitive by changing its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Different Ways to Charge for a Website Project – Freelance Developer Guide]]></title>
        <id>61653c74804854468fda9148</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/different-ways-to-charge-for-a-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T16:37:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As someone who offers a service as a freelancer, you have a major say in how you price a website project. But how do you go about charging for a website project? Sure, you can bill by the hour, but is there a better way? In this article, we are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Your Own Browser Extension [Example Project Included]]]></title>
        <id>617ce33033422e07df3678a3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/write-your-own-browser-extensions/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T15:57:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article we will talk about Browser extensions – what they are, how they work, and how you can build your own. We will finish by actually writing our own extension (Super Fun!) which allows us to copy any code snippet to our clipboard with a click of a single]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rebase vs. Merge: Integrating Changes in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354734</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/rebase-vs-merge-integrating-changes-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T14:19:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is part of our “Advanced Git” series. Be sure to follow us on Twitter or sign up for our newsletter to hear about the next articles!
Most developers understand that it’s important to use branches in Git. In …
The post Rebase vs. Merge: Integrating Changes in Git appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tobias Günther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=355395</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/responsible-javascript-2/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T14:17:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High five to Jeremy on the big release of Responsible JavaScript on A Book Apart. There is a lot of talk about how the proliferation of JavaScript has had a negative impact on the web, but now we have …
The post Responsible JavaScript appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A Magento PWA: Customizing Themes vs. Coding From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/magento-pwa-customizing-themes-coding/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/magento-pwa-customizing-themes-coding/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article sheds the spotlight on Magento PWAs and explains why business owners are getting them (often instead of native applications). Alex Husar introduces ways of how progressive web applications can be developed on Magento, as well as go over the major pros and cons of each development path.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alex Husar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buttons vs. Links]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354978</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/buttons-vs-links/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T22:58:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are thousands of articles out there about buttons and links on the web; the differences and how to use them properly. Hey, I don’t mind. I wrote my own as well¹.
It’s such a common mistake on …
The post Buttons vs. Links appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Have Single-Page Apps Ruined the Web? (“Transitional Apps”)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=355034</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/have-single-page-apps-ruined-the-web-transitional-apps/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T21:43:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A big heaping 19-minute bowl of not-too-hot, not-too-cold baby bear porridge website building from Rich Harris. 
I’ve certainly overheard more than my fair share of arguments about Single Page Apps (SPAs) vs Multi-Page Apps (MPAs). Although it’s only recently that …
The post Have Single-Page Apps Ruined the Web? (“Transitional Apps”) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a gif – Create Animated gifs Without Downloading Software]]></title>
        <id>613f3cba852f4307d372c7e0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-a-gif-create-animated-gifs-without-downloading-software/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T21:31:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A GIF (Graphics Interchange Format) is a small animated image that you can share with your friends and family. And there are many ways to create them without downloading any software. In this article, I will show you how to use the Make a Gif  site, where you can create]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ Vector – STD Pattern Vector in CPP with Example Code]]></title>
        <id>617e651033422e07df36827a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/c-vector-std-pattern-vector-in-cpp-with-example-code/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T21:27:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vectors in C++ are a helpful way to store dynamic data. They also help you avoid having to deal with the not so flexible arrays that are inherited from the C programming language.  This article is a beginner friendly introduction to vectors. It will show you some of their basic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating APIs with Python - Free 19-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>61804dde8bcfae07ca4dfbfd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/creating-apis-with-python-free-19-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T21:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of API tutorials just teach the absolute minimum. But a production-ready API is much more complicated than what most tutorials teach. We just published a massive 19-hour course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build a full-fledged API using Python and the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Authenticate Users in Flask with Flask-Login]]></title>
        <id>617a7da433422e07df3668f0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-authenticate-users-in-flask/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T20:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're developing applications for the general public, it's important to protect your users' credentials and information. This means you need to know about code structure and how to implement various security measures. In this article, we'll walk through the steps to create a user authentication web app with Flask,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Built-in Looping Functions in Python]]></title>
        <id>6114cfae72231b077cdae432</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-looping-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T18:34:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're looping through a sequence in Python like a list, tuple, string, or dictionary, do you ever feel like your code is messy or you want to remove some variables from it?  Fortunately, Python has some useful inbuilt functions which make your code more concise and more readable. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use CodePen – A Beginner&#x27;s Guide]]></title>
        <id>6048a6f0a7946308b7685a2c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-codepen/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T15:47:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CodePen is a popular online code editor used by many developers around the world. It is also one of the recommended editors you can use for the freeCodeCamp curriculum. CodePen is only for frontend projects and supports HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. If you need to build a project with a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So, You Want to Build an @mention Autocomplete Feature?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354588</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/so-you-want-to-build-an-mention-autocomplete-feature/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T14:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re all familiar with the concept of autocompletion, right? You type something into a search box and it tries to guess what you’re looking for as you type, displaying suggestions, often below the cursor. While we’re used to autocomplete on …
The post So, You Want to Build an @mention Autocomplete Feature? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Dayan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS-ing Candy Ghost Buttons]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354804</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-ing-candy-ghost-buttons/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T01:04:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, while looking for some ideas on what to code as I have zero artistic sense so the only thing I can do is find pretty things that other people have come up with and remake them with clean and …
The post CSS-ing Candy Ghost Buttons appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ana Tudor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Splash Of Color For Misty Days (November 2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November is just around the corner, and with it, a new collection of desktop wallpapers to celebrate the beginning of the month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Let’s make November colorful!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Articles About Accessibility I’ve Saved Recently IV]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354581</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-articles-about-accessibility-ive-saved-recently-iv/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T18:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A guide to designing accessible, WCAG-compliant focus indicators — Sara Soueidan says you can make more accessible focus outlines by doing your own, rather than leaving it to the browser — as long as you do it right. Deep dive! 
…
The post Some Articles About Accessibility I’ve Saved Recently IV appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create Your Own Automated Social Images With Resoc]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354296</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/create-your-own-automated-social-images-with-resoc/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T14:14:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There has been a lot of talk about automated social images lately. GitHub has created its own. A WordPress plugin has been acquired by Jetpack. There is definitely interest! People like Ryan Filler and Zach Leatherman have implemented …
The post Create Your Own Automated Social Images With Resoc appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philippe Bernard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[50 Resources And Tools To Turbocharge Your Copywriting Skills]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/resources-tools-turbocharge-copywriting-skills/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/resources-tools-turbocharge-copywriting-skills/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stop wasting time and effort writing copy that falls flat. Raise your copywriting game and boost your powers of persuasion with these rich and informative online resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Freya Giles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Okhsv and Okhsl]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354922</id>
        <link href="https://bottosson.github.io/posts/colorpicker/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T20:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is an old Russian fable where Okhsv and Okhsl are on a rowboat and Okhsv says to Okhsl, “What are the known shortcomings of HSL and HSV color pickers in design applications?” I kid, I kid. But really, what …
The post Okhsv and Okhsl appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vite + _____]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=355166</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/vite-plus-blank/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T18:07:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vite, “Next Generation Frontend Tooling” from Evan You, has been capturing a lot of attention. I’ve heard rave reviews from developers, even in private chats (you gotta try this!). Being from Evan, Vite works great with Vue, …
The post Vite + _____ appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merge Conflicts: What They Are and How to Deal with Them​]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354389</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/merge-conflicts-what-they-are-and-how-to-deal-with-them/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T14:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Merge conflicts... Nobody likes them. Some of us even fear them. But they are a fact of life when you're working with Git, especially when you're teaming up with other developers. In most cases, merge conflicts aren't as scary as you might think. In this fourth part of our “Advanced Git” series we'll talk about when they can happen, what they actually are, and how to solve them.
The post Merge Conflicts: What They Are and How to Deal with Them​ appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tobias Günther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building an Angular Data Grid With Filtering]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354782</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/building-an-angular-data-grid-with-filtering/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T14:03:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
Kendo UI makes it possible to go from a basic idea to a full-fledged app, thanks to a massive component library. We’re talking well over 100 components that are ready for you to drop …
The post Building an Angular Data Grid With Filtering appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An Amazon Product Scraper With Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-amazon-product-scraper-nodejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-amazon-product-scraper-nodejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wealth of data that Amazon holds can make a huge difference when you’re designing a product or hunting for a bargain. But, how can a developer get that data? Simple, by using a web scraper. Here’s how to build your data extraction bot with Node.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Robert Sfichi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sticky Definition Lists]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354777</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/sticky-definition-lists/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T23:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I ran across this 30 seconds of code website the other day, and they have a CSS section which is really good! The first example snippet I looked at was this “floating section headers” example, reminding me yet again how …
The post Sticky Definition Lists appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eye-Tracking In Mobile UX Research]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/eye-tracking-mobile-ux-research/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/eye-tracking-mobile-ux-research/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to technology, eye-tracking has become more accessible to UX research as it allows researchers to get insights about users ’visual attention. This article explores the latest trends in the eye-tracking market and how the methodology can be included in the UX researcher’s toolbox.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mariana Macedo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Next.js Applications With Nx]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/optimizing-nextjs-applications-nx/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/optimizing-nextjs-applications-nx/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nx is a build framework that facilitates optimization, efficient scaling of applications, and other features such as shared libraries and components. In this article, we will be looking at how we can effectively scale Next.js applications by using Nx.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Melvin Kosisochukwu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep Dive Into object-fit And background-size In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/object-fit-background-size-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/object-fit-background-size-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will go through how `object-fit` and `background-size` work, when we can use them, and why, along with some practical use cases and recommendations. Let’s dive in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ahmad Shadeed)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To Quasar Framework: Building Cross-Platform Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/introduction-quasar-framework-cross-platform-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/introduction-quasar-framework-cross-platform-applications/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quasar is an open-source Vue.js-based cross-platform framework that allows you, as a developer, to easily build apps for both desktop and mobile using technologies such as Cordova and Electron and writing your code once. The app we’ll build will store and get its data from Firebase, meaning that we will also be seeing how to use Firebase in Quasar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joel Olawanle)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Real-Time Multi-User Game From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/real-time-multi-user-game/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/real-time-multi-user-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-22T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article highlights the process, technical decisions and lessons learned behind building the real-time game Autowuzzler. Learn how to share game state across multiple clients in real-time with Colyseus, do physics calculations with Matter.js, store data in Supabase.io and build the front-end with SvelteKit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Martin Grubinger)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Respecting Users’ Motion Preferences]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/respecting-users-motion-preferences/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/respecting-users-motion-preferences/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The `prefers-reduced-motion` media query has excellent support in all modern browsers going back a couple of years. In this article, Michelle Barker explains why there’s no reason not to use it today to make your sites more accessible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building The SSG I’ve Always Wanted: An 11ty, Vite And JAM Sandwich]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-ssg-11ty-vite-jam-sandwich/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-ssg-11ty-vite-jam-sandwich/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in January 2020, Ben Holmes set out to do what just about every web developer does each year: rebuild his personal site. In this article, he shares his story of how he set out to build his own build pipeline from absolute ground zero and created “Slinkity”.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Holmes)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building An API With Gatsby Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-api-gatsby-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-api-gatsby-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, Paul Scanlon explains how to build an API by using Gatsby Functions and what you need to keep in mind when deploying it to Gatsby Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 42 With Jeff Smith: What Is DevOps?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/smashing-podcast-episode-42/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/smashing-podcast-episode-42/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about DevOps. What is it, and is it a string to add to your web development bow? Drew McLellan talks to expert Jeff Smith to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solving CLS Issues In A Next.js-Powered E-Commerce Website (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/nextjs-ecommerce-cls-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/nextjs-ecommerce-cls-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cumulative Layout Shift is one of the hardest core web vital to debug. In this article, we go through different tools to investigate CLS, when to use them(and when not), and solutions to some of the CLS issues we faced in our Next.js-based e-commerce website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Arijit Mondal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Simple But Effective Mental Health Routine For Programmers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/effective-mental-health-routine-programmers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/effective-mental-health-routine-programmers/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll look at why taking care of our work-life balance is important, how to develop a simple and effective mental health routine, and the most common and efficient techniques you can use to make your custom routine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dave Oscar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.3]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.3</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.3"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T00:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: broken links in documentation
Chore: Dependency updates
Thank you: @hirdot]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tips And Tricks For Evaluating UX/UI Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/tips-tricks-evaluating-ux-ui-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/tips-tricks-evaluating-ux-ui-designers/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customers may start using your app because you offer a unique product, but user experience is what makes them stay. For that, you need excellent UX designers, and the know-how to spot them when hiring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nataliya Sambir)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart CSS Solutions For Common UI Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/modern-css-solutions-for-common-problems/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/modern-css-solutions-for-common-problems/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing CSS has probably never been more fun and exciting than it is today. In this post we’ll take a look at common problems and use cases we all have to face in our work and how to solve them with modern CSS. If you’re interested, we’ve also just recently covered [CSS auditing tools](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-auditing-tools/), [CSS generators](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-generators/), [front-end boilerplates](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/) and [VS code extensions](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/) — you might find them useful, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming Live Workshops On Front-End & UX (Oct 2021&ndash;Jan 2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/new-smashing-online-workshops-oct-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/new-smashing-online-workshops-oct-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you like a good interface design challenge? What about accessibility testing and design systems? Or maybe Next.js and advanced CSS? With our new online workshops on front-end & design, we cover all of it. Ah, and [here's what our workshops are like](https://vimeo.com/616485526).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful React APIs For Building Flexible Components With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/react-apis-building-flexible-components-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/react-apis-building-flexible-components-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React with JSX is a fantastic tool for making easy-to-use components. Typescript components make it an absolute pleasure for developers to integrate your components into their apps and explore your APIs. Learn about three lesser-known React APIs that can take your components to the next level, and help you build even better React Components in this article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Gaurav Khanna)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bridging The Gap Between Designers And Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/bridging-gap-between-designers-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/bridging-gap-between-designers-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UXPin has recently launched a new feature called “Merge”. This tool aims to break through the chasms of design and development, all while improving the agility and quality our teams expect. This new technology may cause some rethink on how the whole design team and engineering team collaborates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthew Talebi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Autofill Dark Pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/autofill-dark-pattern/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/autofill-dark-pattern/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A “dark pattern” is a deceptive UX pattern that tricks users into doing things they may not really want to do. In this article, Alvaro Montoro does a little experiment to find out how much privacy is taken away from users across three different browsers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alvaro Montoro)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Composable CSS Animation In Vue With AnimXYZ]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/composable-css-animation-vue-animxyz/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/composable-css-animation-vue-animxyz/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most animation libraries like GSAP and Framer Motion are built purely with JavaScript or TypeScript, unlike AnimXYZ, which is labelled “the first composable CSS animation toolkit”, built mainly with SCSS While a simple library, it can be used to achieve a lot of awesome animation on the web in a short amount of time and little code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ejiro Asiuwhu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Static-First MadLib Generator With Portable Text And Netlify On-Demand Builder Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/static-first-madlib-generator-portable-text-netlify-builder-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/static-first-madlib-generator-portable-text-netlify-builder-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be building an interactive fiction experience in which a user can insert words that match parts of speech given by the content creator. Let’s go!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Bryan Robinson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freebie: COVID-19 Icon Set (56 Icons, AI, EPS, SVG, PNG)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/freebie-coronavirus-icon-set/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/freebie-coronavirus-icon-set/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every once in a while, we publish [freebies](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/category/freebies/) related to different occasions and themes. We hope that with this icon set, every designer will be able to find their own use case and contribute to saving lives. Free for personal and commercial use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Anton Tyschenko)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To CSS Debugging]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/guide-debugging-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/guide-debugging-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging in CSS means figuring out what might be the problem when you have unexpected layout results. We’ll look at a few categories bugs often fit into, see how we can evaluate the situation, and explore techniques that help prevent these bugs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local Testing A Serverless API (API Gateway And Lambda)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/local-testing-serverless-api-gateway-lambda/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/local-testing-serverless-api-gateway-lambda/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever struggled with testing cloud services locally? Specifically, have you ever struggled with locally testing an API that uses API Gateway and Lambda, with the Serverless framework, on AWS? In this article, Tom Hudson shares a quick overview of how easy it is to quickly set up your project to test locally before deploying to AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tom Hudson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>