<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-10-12T00:46:29.358Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-10-12T00:46:29.358Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Those “Get The App” Banners]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352907</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/those-get-the-app-banners/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T22:12:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why would a company promote a native app over their perfectly usable website?
We’d have to ask them, I suppose. But it’s hard not to see this push to native as a matter of priorities: that these companies consider native 
…
The post Those “Get The App” Banners appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cash (Tiny jQuery Alternative)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353431</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/cash-tiny-jquery-alternative/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T20:28:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The README for Cash is straightforward:
Cash is an absurdly small jQuery alternative for modern browsers (IE11+) that provides jQuery-style syntax for manipulating the DOM. Utilizing modern browser features to minimize the codebase, developers can use the familiar chainable methods 
…
The post Cash (Tiny jQuery Alternative) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Start a Blog [Free 70-Page Book]]]></title>
        <id>6159ab734aa03507d9412321</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-start-a-blog-book/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T17:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What follows is a full-length book on how to create a successful blog. I am a software developer and I've written 1,500 posts on my blog over the past few years. Millions of people have read my writing. And my blog is now one of the top 20,000]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Dynamic Twitter Header]]></title>
        <id>615408e064aefe07d3fa0743</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-dynamic-twitter-header/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T14:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In mid-2021, a new Twitter design trend emerged: dynamically updated headers. Developers decided that static headers were boring, and dynamic Twitter headers were the way to go.  Ever since then, many developers (including me) have been creating dynamic banners on Twitter. But what does this actually mean? The idea is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Collaboration With Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352569</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/better-collaboration-with-pull-requests/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T14:29:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is part of our “Advanced Git” series. Be sure to follow us on Twitter or sign up for our newsletter to hear about the next articles!
In this third installment of our “Advanced Git” series, we’ll look at …
The post Better Collaboration With Pull Requests appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tobias Günther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Autofill Dark Pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/autofill-dark-pattern/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/autofill-dark-pattern/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A “dark pattern” is a deceptive UX pattern that tricks users into doing things they may not really want to do. In this article, Alvaro Montoro does a little experiment to find out how much privacy is taken away from users across three different browsers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alvaro Montoro)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Composable CSS Animation In Vue With AnimXYZ]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/composable-css-animation-vue-animxyz/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/composable-css-animation-vue-animxyz/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most animation libraries like GSAP and Framer Motion are built purely with JavaScript or TypeScript, unlike AnimXYZ, which is labelled “the first composable CSS animation toolkit”, built mainly with SCSS While a simple library, it can be used to achieve a lot of awesome animation on the web in a short amount of time and little code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ejiro Asiuwhu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Case for ‘Developer Experience’]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353429</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/the-case-for-developer-experience/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T20:23:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A good essay from Jean Yang. 
What I mean by developer experience is the sum total of how developers interface with their tools, end-to-end, day-in and day-out. Sure, there’s more focus than ever on how developers use and adopt tools, and 
…
The post The Case for ‘Developer Experience’ appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Computer Programming?]]></title>
        <id>615d55e60d91c9077974d408</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-programming/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T19:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's world, we are all heavily reliant on various software products that were carefully programmed by developers. But what is computer programming? In this article, I will provide a definition of programming, as well as examples of different types of programmers. I will also suggest a list of courses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn On Dark Mode on Google – Chrome Black Theme Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>6160836e804854468fda67bf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-turn-on-dark-mode-on-google-chrome-black-theme-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T19:10:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, lots of developers like to use dark mode. And it's no surprise, as activating dark mode reduces eye strain and leads to better eye health. It also helps both machines and humans perform better overall.  In this article, I will show you how to turn on the dark]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Drop a Pin on Google Maps]]></title>
        <id>613f3c5e852f4307d372c7c6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-drop-a-pin-on-google-maps/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T19:03:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to save a new location you discovered on Google Maps, you need to drop a pin on that location.  In this article, I will show you how to drop a pin in Google Maps from your phone or computer. How to Drop a Pin on Google Maps]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jekyll doesn’t do components? Liar!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353374</id>
        <link href="https://katiekodes.com/jekyll-components-wysiwyg/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T17:14:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I like the pushback from Katie Kodes here. I’ve said in the past that I don’t think server-side languages haven’t quite nailed “building in components” as well as JavaScript has, but hey, this is a good point:
1. Any basic 
…
The post Jekyll doesn’t do components? Liar! appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an Excel File that Pulls Customer Data with WooCommerce and Python]]></title>
        <id>615dbaeb0d91c9077974defb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-excel-file-with-customers-data-with-woocommerce-and-python/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T15:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Hey, could you please send me our customers' emails? We’re about to launch a new marketing campaign and…we need them ASAP.” If you work in the Web department on a corporate level, you've probably heard this sentence hundreds of times. So, today I want to share how I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Tennis Trivia App With Next.js and Netlify]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353066</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/building-a-tennis-trivia-app-with-next-js-and-netlify/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T14:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we will be learning how to build a tennis trivia app using Next.js and Netlify. This technology stack has become my go-to on many projects. It allows for rapid development and easy deployment.
Without further ado let’s jump in!…
The post Building a Tennis Trivia App With Next.js and Netlify appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brenley Dueck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comparing Google Analytics and Plausible Numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353062</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/comparing-google-analytics-and-plausible-numbers/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T14:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I saw this blog post the other day: 58% of Hacker News, Reddit and tech-savvy audiences block Google Analytics. That’s an enticing title to me. I’ve had Google Analytics on this site literally from the day I launched it. …
The post Comparing Google Analytics and Plausible Numbers appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Static-First MadLib Generator With Portable Text And Netlify On-Demand Builder Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/static-first-madlib-generator-portable-text-netlify-builder-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/static-first-madlib-generator-portable-text-netlify-builder-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be building an interactive fiction experience in which a user can insert words that match parts of speech given by the content creator. Let’s go!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Bryan Robinson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing Your Own Code Rules]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353112</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/writing-your-own-code-rules/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T23:35:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There comes a time on a project when it’s worth investing in tooling to protect the codebase. I’m not sure how to articulate when, but it’s somewhere after the project has proven to be something long-term and rough edges …
The post Writing Your Own Code Rules appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Decisions For Building Flexible Components]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353386</id>
        <link href="https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/developer-decisions-building-flexible-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T21:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blog posts that get into the whole “how to think like a front-end developer” vibe are my favorite. Michelle Barker nails that in this post, and does it without sharing a line of code!
We simply can no longer 
…
The post Developer Decisions For Building Flexible Components appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Go? Golang Programming Language Meaning Explained]]></title>
        <id>615de4da0d91c9077974e23f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-go-programming-language/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T15:26:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Go, also known as Golang, is an open-source, compiled, and statically typed programming language designed by Google. It is built to be simple, high-performing, readable, and efficient.  In this article, you'll learn:  Where Go came from and where it is now, Why I think you should learn it, How to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS in TypeScript with vanilla-extract]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353024</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-in-typescript-with-vanilla-extract/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T14:36:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[vanilla-extract is a new framework-agnostic CSS-in-TypeScript library. It’s a lightweight, robust, and intuitive way to write your styles. vanilla-extract isn’t a prescriptive CSS framework, but a flexible piece of developer tooling. CSS tooling has been a relatively stable space over …
The post CSS in TypeScript with vanilla-extract appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hugh Haworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Themeable React Data Grid With Great UX-Focused Features]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353242</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-themeable-react-data-grid-with-great-ux-focused-features/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T14:35:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
KendoReact can save you boatloads of time because it offers pre-built componentry you can use in your app right away. They look nice, but more importantly, they are easily themeable, so they look however …
The post A Themeable React Data Grid With Great UX-Focused Features appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freebie: COVID-19 Icon Set (56 Icons, AI, EPS, SVG, PNG)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/freebie-coronavirus-icon-set/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/freebie-coronavirus-icon-set/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every once in a while, we publish [freebies](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/category/freebies/) related to different occasions and themes. We hope that with this icon set, every designer will be able to find their own use case and contribute to saving lives. Free for personal and commercial use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Anton Tyschenko)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Websites We Like: MD Nichrome]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353219</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/websites-we-like-md-nichrome/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T22:24:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s a beautiful website: it’s a type specimen for Mass-Driver’s ever-so-lovely type family MD Nichrome. There’s a ton of nifty animations and graphics explaining all the features inside…
If you’re wondering how those animations work, they’re actually styled <video>…
The post Websites We Like: MD Nichrome appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Rendle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Single Page App Morality Play]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353320</id>
        <link href="https://www.baldurbjarnason.com/2021/single-page-app-morality-play/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T22:20:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Baldur Bjarnason brings some baby bear porridge to the discussion of  Single Page App (SPA) vs. Multi Page App (MPA).
Single-Page-Apps can be fantastic. Most teams will mess them up because most teams operate in dysfunctional 
…
The post The Single Page App Morality Play appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C String – How to Declare Strings in the C Programming Language]]></title>
        <id>615beb720d91c9077974c716</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/c-string-how-to-declare-strings-in-the-c-programming-language/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T17:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computers store and process all kinds of data.  Strings are just one of the many forms in which information is presented and gets processed by computers.  Strings in the C programming language work differently than in other modern programming languages.  In this article, you'll learn how to declare strings in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python range() Function – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>612f4388d6679a07b7d3fee4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-range-function-explained-with-code-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T17:21:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, can use use the range() function to get a sequence of indices to loop through an iterable. You'll often use range() in conjunction with a for loop.  In this tutorial, you'll learn about the different ways in which you can use the range() function – with explicit start and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux tar Command – How to Compress Files in Linux]]></title>
        <id>614870b9852f4307d3731030</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-compress-files-in-linux-with-tar-command/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T16:19:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[File compression is an essential utility across all platforms. It helps you reduce file size and share files efficiently. And compressed files are also easier to copy to remote servers.  You can also compress older and rarely used files and save them for future use which helps you conserve disk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Considerations for Using Markdown Writing Apps on Static Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352959</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/considerations-for-using-markdown-writing-apps-on-static-sites/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T14:22:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you run or have recently switched to a static site generator, you might find yourself writing a lot of Markdown. And the more you write it, the more you want the tooling experience to disappear so that …
The post Considerations for Using Markdown Writing Apps on Static Sites appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leon Barnard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Options for Password Revealing Inputs]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352676</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-options-for-password-revealing-inputs/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T14:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In HTML, there is a very clear input type for dealing with passwords:
<input type="password">
If you use that, you get the obfuscated bullet-points when you type into it, like:
••••••••
That’s the web trying to help with security. If …
The post The Options for Password Revealing Inputs appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To CSS Debugging]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/guide-debugging-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/guide-debugging-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging in CSS means figuring out what might be the problem when you have unexpected layout results. We’ll look at a few categories bugs often fit into, see how we can evaluate the situation, and explore techniques that help prevent these bugs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local Testing A Serverless API (API Gateway And Lambda)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/local-testing-serverless-api-gateway-lambda/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/local-testing-serverless-api-gateway-lambda/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever struggled with testing cloud services locally? Specifically, have you ever struggled with locally testing an API that uses API Gateway and Lambda, with the Serverless framework, on AWS? In this article, Tom Hudson shares a quick overview of how easy it is to quickly set up your project to test locally before deploying to AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tom Hudson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An Expandable Accessible Gallery]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/build-expandable-accessible-gallery/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/build-expandable-accessible-gallery/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be looking at how to set up a gallery that is expandable as well as accessible with a few tips and tricks along the way. Let’s get started!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Silvestar Bistrović)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Search Functionality In Your Nuxt App Using Algolia InstantSearch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/search-functionality-nuxt-app-algolia-instantsearch/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/search-functionality-nuxt-app-algolia-instantsearch/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many websites have some sort of search feature because it helps users navigate through their content easily. Implementing it the right way can be tricky and might not give a good user experience. In this tutorial, we will be integrating Algolia, a popular and powerful search service for the best experience on our Nuxt site.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Miracle Onyenma)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Time Of Transition (October 2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-30T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get your desktop ready for fall and the upcoming Halloween season with a fresh batch of desktop wallpapers. Created with love by designers and artists from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for October 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Modern Image Formats: AVIF And WebP]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/modern-image-formats-avif-webp/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/modern-image-formats-avif-webp/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T08:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll highlight how modern image formats (AVIF or WebP) can improve compression by up to 50% and deliver better quality per-byte while still looking visually appealing. We’ll compare what’s possible at high-quality, low-quality and file-size targets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Accessibility Of Your Markdown]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/improving-accessibility-of-markdown/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/improving-accessibility-of-markdown/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can find Markdown in many places on the Internet. This article covers different aspects of Markdown and how it interacts with other technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Dive Into Cypress For End-to-End Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/cypress-end-to-end-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/cypress-end-to-end-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is end-to-end testing a painful topic for you? In this article, Ramona Schwering explains how to handle end-to-end testing with Cypress and make it make it not so tedious and expensive for yourself, but fun instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ramona Schwering)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.2"/>
        <updated>2021-09-26T18:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: unicode characters in URL caused download error
Fixed: project root npm install error
Added: unit test library
Chore: Dependency updates
Thank you: @CaptNo1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rebuilding A Large E-Commerce Website With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/lessons-learned-ecommerce-nextjs-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/lessons-learned-ecommerce-nextjs-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We made the switch from a more traditional integrated e-commerce platform to a headless platform with Next.js. Here are the most important lessons learned while rebuilding a large e-commerce site with Next.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jonne Kats)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Online Workshop: Frustrating Design Patterns And How To Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/smashing-workshop-frustrating-design-patterns/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/smashing-workshop-frustrating-design-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T06:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve seen them before. Confusing and frustrating design patterns that seem to be chasing you everywhere you go, from one website to another. It’s time to fix them for good in a [free Smashing online workshop](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/workshops/vitaly-friedman-frustrating-patterns/) next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplifying Form Styles With `accent-color`]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/simplifying-form-styles-accent-color/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/simplifying-form-styles-accent-color/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new CSS `accent-color` property makes it quick and easy to roll out our brand colors to certain form inputs by leveraging user agent styles. In this article we’ll take a look at what it does and how to use it alongside `color-scheme` for simple, accessible checkboxes and radio buttons — and imagine how we might use it in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Your `head` Straight: A New CSS Performance Diagnostics Snippet]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/css-head-tag/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/css-head-tag/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We love little useful tools and techniques to help folks get their work done better and faster. Today, we’d love to shine the spotlights on a little helper that helps spot common performance bottlenecks easily: [ct.css](https://csswizardry.com/ct/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build Your Own Mouseless Development Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/mouseless-development-environment/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/mouseless-development-environment/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a development environment with the shell as a keystone offers multiple benefits. You can customize everything depending on your own needs, and the biggest of all, you can control your entire development environment with your keyboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthieu Cneude)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Web Development Tools Are Helping Users Keep Pace With Rapid Change]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-development-tools-users-keep-pace-rapid-change/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-development-tools-users-keep-pace-rapid-change/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last 18 months have been a time of unprecedented turbulence. As the people of the world have flooded online, businesses have joined them, using web development tools to adapt in real-time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Imposter Domains Re-Publishing Your Website?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/imposter-domains-republishing-website/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/imposter-domains-republishing-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content scraping is a fact of life on the Internet. When you think of web scraping, you probably do not think about the scrapers turning around and immediately serving your entire, whole page content on another website. But what if your site content is being re-published?  It might be already happening.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ken Harker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monetize Open-Source Software With Gatsby Functions And Stripe]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/monetize-open-source-software-gatsby-functions-stripe/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/monetize-open-source-software-gatsby-functions-stripe/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Functions provide front-end developers a way to write and use server-side code without the hassle of maintaining a server. If making money from open-source is of interest to you and your site isn’t built using Gatsby, this approach may well be the answer you were looking for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Quality Assurance: From User Requirements To Web Risk Management]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/journey-into-web-quality-assurance/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/journey-into-web-quality-assurance/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twenty years ago, Elie Sloïm chose to dedicate his professional life to web quality assurance. He started asking, ”What does quality mean for a web user?” Well, this article explains everything he has learned along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Elie Sloïm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reasons To Build A CRM-Powered Website For Your Business]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reasons-build-crm-powered-website-business/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reasons-build-crm-powered-website-business/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating a CRM with your business website has numerous benefits. In this article, Zara Cooper explains what these benefits are and why websites should be integrated with a CRM platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.1"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T06:39:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Unexpected nested element in author field crashes the parser
Thank you @ad-m]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing The Need For Pseudo-Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reducing-need-pseudo-elements/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reducing-need-pseudo-elements/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, pseudo-elements have faithfully helped front-end developers implement creative designs. While they still have an important place, we can now leave pseudo-elements behind in some scenarios, thanks to newer CSS properties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcel Moreau)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Power Of Pen And Paper Sketching]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/power-pen-paper-sketching/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/power-pen-paper-sketching/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing for digital spaces, it’s natural to default to digital mockup tools, but doing so cuts out a world of possibilities. Analog drawing can unleash your imagination and allow you to focus on what’s most important at the start: the ideas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tracy Osborn)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orchestrating Complexity With Web Animations API]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/orchestrating-complexity-web-animations-api/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/orchestrating-complexity-web-animations-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are way too many options in Web Animations API to pick them up that easily. Learning how timing works and how to control the playback of several animations at once makes for a solid foundation on which to base your projects on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kirill Myshkin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>