<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-08-22T00:38:10.135Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-08-22T00:38:10.135Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Disambiguating Tailwind”]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=350186</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/disambiguating-tailwind/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-20T19:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I appreciated this bit of nuance from a post on Viget’s blog:
There could be a whole article written about the many flavours of Tailwind, but broadly speaking those flavours are:
1. Stock tailwind, ie. no changes to the 
…
The post “Disambiguating Tailwind” appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Coding Interview – How to Stand Out and Ace the Challenges]]></title>
        <id>611fd94c3bccf807612a4160</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-stand-out-during-your-react-coding-interview/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-20T18:20:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a React developer, I have gone through my fair share of front-end coding interviews. Recently, I had the opportunity to experience the process from the other side – as an interviewer. Here is what I've learned. Coding interview usually involve a multi-step process where interviewers assess everything from basic technical]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Truly Reusable React Component from Scratch]]></title>
        <id>611bf4f8e884de0752180979</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-truly-reusable-react-component-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-20T17:54:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will build an app with React. And you will learn how to create a truly reusable auto-suggestion component from scratch. This application will allow a user to search for a country in a list of countries. It will display matching suggestions below the input field for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Line Break – How to Break a Line with the HTML &lt;br&gt; Tag]]></title>
        <id>611f9b083bccf807612a3df0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-line-break-how-to-break-a-line-with-the-html-br-tag/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-20T17:21:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're writing HTML, you often need to insert line breaks. A line break is essential in addresses, poems, or when text exceeds the available browser width. If you don't insert your own line breaks, then the text gets formatted in an odd way.  In this tutorial, I'm going to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a Headless WordPress Site With Frontity]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346702</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-headless-wordpress-site-with-frontity/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-20T14:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontity is a WordPress-focused React-based server-side dynamic-rendering framework (phew!) that allows us to create fast headless websites. Chris has a good introduction to Frontity. I guess you could think of it like Next.js for WordPress. And while the demand …
The post Creating a Headless WordPress Site With Frontity appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Dahal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jamstack CMS: The Past, The Present and The Future]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/history-future-jamstack-cms/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/history-future-jamstack-cms/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-20T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The story of Jamstack CMSs goes all the way back to the 90s. In this article, we take a trip down memory lane to see how we got to the modern Jamstack CMSs we have today, and where they’re heading in the next decade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mike Neumegen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming, Math, and Statistics You Need to Know for Data Science and Machine Learning]]></title>
        <id>611d56d3e884de07521810f9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/first-steps-to-learn-data-science-or-ml-after-the-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-20T03:21:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the start of this year, I published a mind map on the Data Science learning roadmap (shown below). Many people found the roadmap useful, my article got translated into different languages, and a large number of folks thanked me for publishing it. Everything was good until a few developers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Font Style – How to Change Text Color and Size with an HTML Tag]]></title>
        <id>611e8bac3bccf807612a34df</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-font-style-how-to-change-text-color-and-size-with-an-html-tag/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-19T23:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you code in HTML and add some text, you don’t want to leave it like that. You want to make that text look good.  And to do that, you need to change their appearance through the color and font-size properties of CSS.  In this tutorial, I will show]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Display Property – Display None, Display Table, Inline Block and More]]></title>
        <id>611d436ee884de0752181044</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-css-display-property-display-none-display-table-inline-block-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-19T20:47:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In CSS, the display property determines how an element looks. It is also a crucial part of the presentation of you HTML code as it has a significant impact on layouts.  In fact, to use the modern Flexbox and Grid models, you need to use the display property before you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lexical Scope in JavaScript – What Exactly Is Scope in JS?]]></title>
        <id>611e4447e884de0752181578</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-lexical-scope-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-19T19:56:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “lexical scope” may seem tricky to grasp at first glance. But it's helpful to understand what each word means. So this article will explain lexical scope by first examining the meaning of “lexical” and “scope”. So, let’s get it started by understanding the term “scope”. What exactly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Big Gotcha With Custom Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=350054</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-big-gotcha-with-custom-properties/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-19T19:04:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve seen this confuse more than a handful of people recently, including myself, so I’m making sure it’s written down.
Let’s chuck a couple of custom properties into CSS:
html {
  --color-1: red;
  --color-2: blue;
}
Let’s use them right …
The post The Big Gotcha With Custom Properties appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Space – How to Add a Non-breaking Space with the &amp;nbsp; Character Entity]]></title>
        <id>611e3f8ee884de0752181566</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-space-how-to-add-a-non-breaking-space-with-the-nbsp-character-entity/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-19T17:29:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In HTML, you can't create an extra blank space after the space ( ) character with the spacebar. If you want 10 blank spaces in your HTML code and you try to add them with the spacebar, you'll only see one space in the browser.  Also, one or more of the words]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Array.map() Tutorial – How to Iterate Through Elements in an Array with map()]]></title>
        <id>611d2ad1e884de0752180f58</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/array-map-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-19T16:16:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When ES6 (EmcaScript 2015) came out, it ushered in a whole new set of methods for iterating over an array. And one of the most useful is the map() method. Array.prototype.map() is a built-in array method for iterating through the elements inside an array collection in JavaScript. Think]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Nuxt and Supabase for  a Multi-User Blogging App]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346563</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-nuxt-and-supabase-for-a-multi-user-blogging-app/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-19T14:32:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nuxt is a JavaScript framework that extends the existing functionality of Vue.js with features like server-side rendering, static page generation, file-based routing, and automatic code splitting among other things.
I’ve been enjoying using frameworks like Nuxt and Next because they …
The post Using Nuxt and Supabase for  a Multi-User Blogging App appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nader Dabit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing a single GraphQL across multiple data sources]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=350035</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/implementing-a-single-graphql-across-multiple-data-sources/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-19T14:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
In this article, we will discuss how we can apply schema stitching across multiple Fauna instances. We will also discuss how to combine other GraphQL services and data sources with Fauna in one graph.…
The post Implementing a single GraphQL across multiple data sources appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shadid Haque</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the Java Native Interface - Free 28-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>6116c31e72231b077cdafc89</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-java-native-interface-free-28-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-19T12:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Java Native Interface allows Java code to call native libraries written in C and C++. It is helpful when you need to do something that cannot be accomplished with Java alone. We just released a massive 28-Hour course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will take you from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An Ethical User Research Practice At Any Organization]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/ethical-user-research-practice/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/ethical-user-research-practice/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Through a simple step-by-step approach, you can build an ethical practice within your organization that will ensure you’re respecting the dignity and welfare of your research participants.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Devin Harold)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“We had 90% unused CSS because everybody was afraid to touch the old stuff”]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=348288</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/we-had-90-unused-css-because-everybody-was-afraid-to-touch-the-old-stuff/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-18T22:16:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over at the JS Party podcast:
[Kend C. Dodds]: […] ask anybody who’s done regular, old CSS and they’ll tell you that “I don’t know if it’s okay for me to change this, so I’m gonna duplicate it.” And now 
…
The post “We had 90% unused CSS because everybody was afraid to touch the old stuff” appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Native Search vs. Jetpack Instant Search in Headless WordPress With Gatsby]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346147</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/native-search-vs-jetpack-instant-search-in-headless-wordpress-with-gatsby/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-18T14:46:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you already tried using WordPress headlessly with Gatsby? If you haven’t, you might check this article around the new Gatsby source plugin for WordPress; gatsby-source-wordpress is the official source plugin introduced in March 2021 as a part of the …
The post Native Search vs. Jetpack Instant Search in Headless WordPress With Gatsby appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paulina Hetman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating An Interactive Gantt Chart Component With Vanilla JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/interactive-gantt-chart-component-vanilla-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/interactive-gantt-chart-component-vanilla-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-18T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will code a Gantt chart as a reusable Web component. We will focus on the architecture of the component, rendering the calendar with CSS Grid and managing the state of the draggable tasks with JavaScript Proxy Objects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Anna Prenzel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DX, to Whom?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346697</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/dx-to-whom/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-17T21:09:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dave points to Sarah’s post on Developer Experience (DX) at Netlify. Part of what Sarah did there is lay out what the role means. It’s a three-part thing:
Integrations Engineering (e.g. features)
Developer Experience Engineering (e.g. building integrations 
…
The post DX, to Whom? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From a Single Repo, to Multi-Repos, to Monorepo, to Multi-Monorepo]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346449</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/from-a-single-repo-to-multi-repos-to-monorepo-to-multi-monorepo/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-17T14:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been working on the same project for several years. Its initial version was a huge monolithic app containing thousands of files. It was poorly architected and non-reusable, but was hosted in a single repo making it easy to work …
The post From a Single Repo, to Multi-Repos, to Monorepo, to Multi-Monorepo appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leonardo Losoviz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Open-Source Icons]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/open-source-icons/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/open-source-icons/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-17T07:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your project is on a tight budget? We’ve collected some wonderful, free icons and goodies that we’ve discovered lately and that are bound to give your design the finishing touch. We’ve also just recently covered [Figma plugins](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/figma-tools-plugins-resources/), [SVG generators](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/svg-generators/), [accessible front-end components](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/complete-guide-accessible-front-end-components/) and [front-end boilerplates](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/) — you might find them useful, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tabs in HTML?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346418</id>
        <link href="https://bkardell.com/blog/SpicySections.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-16T23:31:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brian Kardell shares a bit about the progress of bringing "Tabs" to HTML. We kinda think we know what they are, but you have to be really specific when dealing with specs and defining them. It's tricky.
The post Tabs in HTML? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cutouts]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346686</id>
        <link href="https://ishadeed.com/article/thinking-about-the-cut-out-effect/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-16T20:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahmad Shadeed dug into shape “cutouts” the other day. Imagine a shape with another smaller shape carved out of it. In his typical comprehensive way, Ahmad laid out the situation well—looking at tricky situations that complicate things. 
The first thing …
The post Cutouts appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML is Not a Programming Language?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346318</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/html-is-not-a-programming-language/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-16T14:44:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML is not a programming language.
I’ve heard that sentence so many times and it’s tiring. Normally, it is followed by something like, It doesn’t have logic, or, It is not Turing complete,.so… obviously it is not a programming …
The post HTML is Not a Programming Language? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvaro Montoro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Develop Your Business’ Technology Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/develop-business-technology-roadmap/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/develop-business-technology-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-16T06:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software development without a roadmap is akin to driving off a cliff — an undertaking that seriously jeopardizes your product’s life. Here’s how to develop a business technology roadmap that ensures your project safely reaches its final destination.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cache Merril)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unicode Arrows]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346665</id>
        <link href="https://unicodearrows.com/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-13T18:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looks like… 253 of them. I love the little water ⥾ spout one. (U+297e). Because. And I like how it’s a fairly useful little site at a great domain and with a little business model behind it. …
The post Unicode Arrows appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Cool Front End Thing Generator]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345944</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/building-a-cool-front-end-thing-generator/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-13T14:41:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you are just starting out on the front end, or you’ve been doing it for a long time, building a tool that can generate some cool front-end magic can help you learn something new, develop your skills and maybe …
The post Building a Cool Front End Thing Generator appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Polacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stay alert]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346608</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/richharris/stay-alert-d"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T21:10:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few days ago, Chris wrote up his thoughts about how alert(), confirm(), and prompt() were being deprecated by Chrome and collected a bunch of thoughts from developers. If certain features can essentially be turned off by …
The post Stay alert appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Rendle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Figma Plugins And Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/Figma-tools-plugins-resources/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/Figma-tools-plugins-resources/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Figma plugins that will help you fix all the little slowdowns and boost your productivity. From color management and image assets to SVG shapes and animation. That’s our new guide to Figma.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Janet John)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Smashing Workshops on Front-End & Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/new-smashing-online-workshops-aug-oct-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/new-smashing-online-workshops-aug-oct-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-11T13:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do we build and establish a successful, bulletproof design system? What’s the state of HTML Email? And what are new, smart interface design patterns we could use? Let’s find out. With our [brand new online workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) on front-end & design — to help us all boost skills online.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Handling Mounting And Unmounting Of Navigation Routes In React Native]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/mounting-unmounting-navigation-routes-react-native/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/mounting-unmounting-navigation-routes-react-native/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-11T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Often you need two different sets of navigation stacks for pre and post user authentication. Usually, to see more content, you have to be authenticated in some way. Let’s look at how to mount and unmount navigation stack based on a met condition in React Native.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Daniel Don)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cookieless Alternative To Embed HTML, CSS And JS Code Snippets]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/cookieless-alternative-embed-html-css-js-code-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/cookieless-alternative-embed-html-css-js-code-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Embedding code examples with third-party scripts often leads to tracking or cookies. We always wanted to have a simple website with a good UX, so setting cookies for no reason wasn’t an option for us. Now, with Indiepen, we are proud to introduce a privacy-friendly alternative.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Henrik Fricke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 41 With Eva PenzeyMoog: Designing For Safety]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/smashing-podcast-episode-41/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/smashing-podcast-episode-41/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about designing for safety. What does it mean to consider vulnerable users in our designs? Drew McLellan talks to expert Eva PenzeyMoog to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP/3 From A To Z: Core Concepts (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/http3-core-concepts-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/http3-core-concepts-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What exactly is HTTP/3? Why was it needed so soon after HTTP/2 (which was only finalized in 2015)? How can or should you use it? And especially, how does this improve web performance? Let’s find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Robin Marx)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Useful VSCode Extensions For Web Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/useful-vscode-extensions-web-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/useful-vscode-extensions-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code can be supercharged wuth hundreds of [VS Code extensions](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/). In this article, Leonardo shares four useful extensions that help him in his daily work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Disabled Buttons]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/frustrating-design-patterns-disabled-buttons/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/frustrating-design-patterns-disabled-buttons/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can we make disabled buttons more inclusive? When do they work well, and when do they fail on us? And finally, when do we actually need them, and how can we avoid them? Let’s find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Children And Iteration Methods]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/react-children-iteration-methods/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/react-children-iteration-methods/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll discuss and learn about the use case of iterating over React `children` and the ways to do it. In particular, we will deep dive into one of the utility methods, `React.Children.toArray`, that React gives us, which helps to iterate over the children in a way which ensures performance and determinism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Arihant Verma)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build Resilient JavaScript UIs]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/build-resilient-javascript-ui/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/build-resilient-javascript-ui/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Resilience is intrinsic to the web and therefore us, web developers. This article explores how graceful degradation, defensive coding, observability, and a healthy attitude towards failures better equips us before, during, and after an error occurs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Callum Hart)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring CSS: Strategy, Regression Testing And Maintenance (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/refactoring-css-strategy-regression-testing-maintenance-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/refactoring-css-strategy-regression-testing-maintenance-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll take a deep dive into the refactoring process itself, and cover incremental refactoring strategy, visual regression testing, and maintaining the refactored codebase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Vibes In August (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New month, new wallpapers! In this post, you’ll find unique and inspiring wallpapers for August 2021. Created with love by the community for the community, they come in versions with and without a calendar for the month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An E-Commerce Site With Angular 11, Commerce Layer And Paypal]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/ecommerce-angular11-headless-paypal/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/ecommerce-angular11-headless-paypal/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having an e-commerce store is crucial for any store owner as more and more customers are turning to online shopping. In this tutorial, we shall go through how to create an e-commerce site with Angular 11. The site will use the Commerce Layer as a headless e-commerce API and use Paypal to process payments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Is No Such Thing As A CSS Absolute Unit]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/css-absolute-units/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/css-absolute-units/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are absolute units? What are the differences between relative and absolute units, and how do we create accurate sizes on the web? In this article, Elad Shechter explains why CSS absolute units aren’t so absolute.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Elad Shechter)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating An Accessible Dialog From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/accessible-dialog-from-scratch/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/accessible-dialog-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dialogs are everywhere in modern interface design (for good or for bad), and yet many of them are not accessible to assistive technologies. In this article, we will dig into how to create a short script to create accessible dialogs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kitty Giraudel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global vs. Local Styling In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/global-local-styling-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/global-local-styling-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js has strong opinions about how to organize JavaScript but not CSS. How can we develop patterns that encourage best CSS practices while also following the framework’s logic? The answer is surprisingly simple — to write well-structured CSS that balances global and local styling concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alexander Dubovoy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Serverless Functions And The International Space Station]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/gatsby-serverless-functions-international-space-station/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/gatsby-serverless-functions-international-space-station/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby recently announced the launch of “functions”. In this article, Paul Scanlon explains how to get the current location of the International Space Station (ISS) as it orbits the Earth in real-time using [Gatsby Functions](https://www.gatsbyjs.com/docs/reference/functions/) and then display it on a 3D interactive globe using [React Three Fibre](https://github.com/pmndrs/react-three-fiber).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>