<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-09-30T00:47:08.483Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-09-30T00:47:08.483Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Count – How to Select, Sum, and Average Rows in SQL]]></title>
        <id>612cbfe4b5177808226d4a4b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-count-how-to-select-sum-and-average-rows-in-sql/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T20:04:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In SQL, there are two built-in functions to sum or average the data in your table.  In this article I will show you how to use the SUM and AVG functions in SQL using code examples.  How to use the SUM function in SQLIf you need to add a group]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Accordion Menu Using HTML, CSS and JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>615440ac64aefe07d3fa0855</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-accordion-menu-using-html-css-and-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T19:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use HTML, CSS and JavaScript to create stylish and dynamic web elements. And one useful element you can build is an accordion menu. Accordion menus expand and collapse when a user clicks a button. It's a great way to not have to show all the info about a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Comment – How to Comment Out a Line or Tag in HTML]]></title>
        <id>6154412664aefe07d3fa085b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-comment-how-to-comment-out-a-line-or-tag-in-html/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T17:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll learn how to add single and multi-line comments to your HTML documents.  You'll also see why comments are considered a good practice when writing HTML code.  Let's get started!  The HTML Comment Tag The general syntax for an HTML comment looks like this:  <!-- I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Streams Everywhere (and Fetch for Node.js)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352723</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/web-streams-everywhere-and-fetch-for-node-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T14:51:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome developer advocate Jake Archibald called 2016 “the year of web streams.” Clearly, his prediction was somewhat premature. The Streams Standard was announced back in 2014. It’s taken a while, but there’s now a consistent streaming API implemented …
The post Web Streams Everywhere (and Fetch for Node.js) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ollie Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Front-End Dev Shortcuts in iOS 15]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352627</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/front-end-dev-shortcuts-in-ios-15/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T14:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was pretty stoked when Chris shared a way to “View Source” on mobile. Sure, it’s not the same as a built-in feature but it allows iOS users like myself a way to peek at a site’s code the …
The post Front-End Dev Shortcuts in iOS 15 appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Modern Image Formats: AVIF And WebP]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/modern-image-formats-avif-webp/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/modern-image-formats-avif-webp/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T08:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll highlight how modern image formats (AVIF or WebP) can improve compression by up to 50% and deliver better quality per-byte while still looking visually appealing. We’ll compare what’s possible at high-quality, low-quality and file-size targets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Flexbox Tutorial – How to Build a Fixed Side and Bottom Navbar]]></title>
        <id>614e7e50ccc97307eb2bc3e5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fixed-side-and-bottom-navbar-with-css-flexbox/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T21:41:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flexbox can help you simplify the process of creating both basic and advanced layouts. And it's pretty straightforward to create side and bottom navigation menus with CSS flexbox or Grid. These layouts are so popular that they appear almost everywhere on the web. For example, check out Twitter's sidebar, which]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So many little design helper sites!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352669</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/so-many-little-design-helper-sites/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T21:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had one of those little single-serving designer helper sites bookmarked the other day: getwaves.io. Randomized SVG waves! Lots of cool options! Easy to customize! Easy to copy and paste! Well played, z creative labs. 

But then I …
The post So many little design helper sites! appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML / CSS Tutorial - Build a Recipe Website]]></title>
        <id>6153616d64aefe07d3fa049a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-css-tutorial-build-a-recipe-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T18:56:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building projects is a great way to build your skills, especially when it comes to web development. We just published an HTML & CSS course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel teach you how to build a recipe website. John Smilga developed this course. He is one of the most]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Publish an HTML Website on Netlify or GitHub Pages]]></title>
        <id>613c75b1852f4307d372b9ab</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/publish-your-website-netlify-github/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T17:36:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You have finished creating your HTML website and you're feeling proud of your hard work. But there is one thing that is still missing: you have no idea how to publish your website. In this tutorial, you will learn how to publish an HTML website using two popular platforms – Netlify]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Sentry to Your Node.js Project with TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>615233ec64aefe07d3f9fdb4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-sentry-to-your-node-js-project-with-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T16:24:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sentry.io is an external monitoring and logging service which can help you identify and triage errors in your code.  These logs provide information such as a trace stack, breadcrumbs, and (assuming this is a web application) browser data. This can help you triage issues and resolve bugs faster, with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Semantic HTML Guide – 10 Alternatives to Using divs]]></title>
        <id>614e05eeccc97307eb2bc165</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/semantic-html-alternatives-to-using-divs/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T16:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Raise your hand if your typical HTML layout looks like this: <body> 	<div class="header" id="site-header"> 		<div class="site-nav"> 			<ul> 				<li><a href="/">Home</a></li> 				<li><a href="/">]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iOS Browser Choice]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352681</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/ios-browser-choice/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T14:26:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just last week I got one of those really?! 🤨 faces when this fact came up in conversation amongst smart and engaged fellow web developers: there is no browser choice on iOS. It’s all Safari. You can download apps that …
The post iOS Browser Choice appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Unleashed is Back! (Use Coupon Code “CSS-Tricks” for 50% Off)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352073</id>
        <link href="https://fitc.ca/event/webu21/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T14:24:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
Now in its tenth year (!!!), Web Unleashed is one of the top events for web devs. It’s coming up quick: October 20-22, 2021. 
The lineup is amazing. You’ll hear from leaders in …
The post Web Unleashed is Back! (Use Coupon Code “CSS-Tricks” for 50% Off) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Accessibility Of Your Markdown]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/improving-accessibility-of-markdown/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/improving-accessibility-of-markdown/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can find Markdown in many places on the Internet. This article covers different aspects of Markdown and how it interacts with other technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Repo Guide – How to Increase Engagement on your Public GitHub Repositories]]></title>
        <id>6149e65e9456b407b870fdc5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/increase-engagement-on-your-public-github-repositories/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T00:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub is a collection of web-based tools that helps you work with version control and Git methodologies.  With the help of GitHub, you can create, manage, and collaborate on projects with multiple other team members. You keep the project folders and files in a store (file system) on GitHub. This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Emojis – Emoji List for Copy and Paste]]></title>
        <id>613b2c1a852f4307d372b02f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/all-emojis-emoji-list-for-copy-and-paste/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T21:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emoji help you express feelings and emotions beyond texts. They also bring liveliness into conversations in a fun and concise way.  But sometimes it's hard to find the right emoji to use, so I decided to prepare a giant table of them that you can simply copy and paste into]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tonic (Component Framework)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352621</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/tonic-component-framework/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T18:52:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I enjoy little frameworks like Tonic. It’s essentially syntactic sugar over <web-components /> to make them feel easier to use. Define a Class, template literal an HTML template, probably some other fancy helpers, and you’ve got a component …
The post Tonic (Component Framework) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collecting Email Signups With the Notion API]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352211</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/collecting-email-signups-with-the-notion-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T15:26:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of people these days are setting up their own newsletters. You’ve got the current big names like Substack and MailChimp, companies like Twitter are getting into it with Revue, and even Facebook is getting into the …
The post Collecting Email Signups With the Notion API appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ravgeet Dhillon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Dive Into Cypress For End-to-End Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/cypress-end-to-end-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/cypress-end-to-end-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is end-to-end testing a painful topic for you? In this article, Ramona Schwering explains how to handle end-to-end testing with Cypress and make it make it not so tedious and expensive for yourself, but fun instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ramona Schwering)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.2"/>
        <updated>2021-09-26T18:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: unicode characters in URL caused download error
Fixed: project root npm install error
Added: unit test library
Chore: Dependency updates
Thank you: @CaptNo1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Systems for z-index]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352287</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/systems-for-z-index/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T21:19:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Say you have a z-index bug. Something is being covered up by something else. In my experience, a typical solution is to put position: relative on the thing so z-index works in the first place, and maybe rejigger the z-index…
The post Systems for z-index appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Self Provisioning Runtime]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352533</id>
        <link href="https://www.swyx.io/self-provisioning-runtime/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T18:56:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Big thoughts on where the industry is headed from Shawn Wang:
Advancements in two fields — programming languages and cloud infrastructure — will converge in a single paradigm: where all resources required by a program will be automatically provisioned, and 
…
The post The Self Provisioning Runtime appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comparing Methods for Appending and Inserting With JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352342</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/comparing-methods-for-appending-and-inserting-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T14:34:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s say we want to add something to a webpage after the initial load. JavaScript gives us a variety of tools. Perhaps you’ve used some of them, like append, appendChild, insertAdjacentHTML, or innerHTML.
The difficult thing …
The post Comparing Methods for Appending and Inserting With JavaScript appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Markfield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Learning Partner: Frontend Masters]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=351975</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/our-learning-partner-frontend-masters-2/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T14:34:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend Masters has been our learning partner for a couple of years now. I love it. If you need structured learning to up your web development skills, Frontend Masters is the place. It works so well because we don’t offer …
The post Our Learning Partner: Frontend Masters appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rebuilding A Large E-Commerce Website With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/lessons-learned-ecommerce-nextjs-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/lessons-learned-ecommerce-nextjs-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We made the switch from a more traditional integrated e-commerce platform to a headless platform with Next.js. Here are the most important lessons learned while rebuilding a large e-commerce site with Next.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jonne Kats)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Online Workshop: Frustrating Design Patterns And How To Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/smashing-workshop-frustrating-design-patterns/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/smashing-workshop-frustrating-design-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T06:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve seen them before. Confusing and frustrating design patterns that seem to be chasing you everywhere you go, from one website to another. It’s time to fix them for good in a [free Smashing online workshop](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/workshops/vitaly-friedman-frustrating-patterns/) next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Your Page Title on a Google Search Engine Results Page?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352279</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-is-your-page-title-on-a-google-search-engine-results-page/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T18:11:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whatever Google wants it to be. I always thought it was exactly what your <title> element was. Perhaps in lieu of that, what the first <h1> on the page is. But recently I noticed some pages on this site that …
The post What is Your Page Title on a Google Search Engine Results Page? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Working With GraphQL Caching]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352381</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/working-with-graphql-caching/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T14:32:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve recently started working with GraphQL, or reviewed its pros and cons, you’ve no doubt heard things like “GraphQL doesn’t support caching” or “GraphQL doesn’t care about caching.” And for most, that is a big deal.
The official …
The post Working With GraphQL Caching appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Barton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How to Build True Edge Apps With Cloudflare Workers and Fauna]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352487</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/learn-how-to-build-true-edge-apps-with-cloudflare-workers-and-fauna/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T14:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
There is a lot of buzz around apps running on the edge instead of on a centralized server in web development. Running your app on the edge allows your code to be closer to …
The post Learn How to Build True Edge Apps With Cloudflare Workers and Fauna appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Jackson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplifying Form Styles With `accent-color`]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/simplifying-form-styles-accent-color/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/simplifying-form-styles-accent-color/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new CSS `accent-color` property makes it quick and easy to roll out our brand colors to certain form inputs by leveraging user agent styles. In this article we’ll take a look at what it does and how to use it alongside `color-scheme` for simple, accessible checkboxes and radio buttons — and imagine how we might use it in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Container Units Should Be Pretty Handy]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352210</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/container-units-should-be-pretty-handy/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T23:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Container queries are going to solve this long-standing issue in web design where we want to make design choices based on the size of an element (the container) rather than the size of the entire page. So, if a container …
The post Container Units Should Be Pretty Handy appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Your `head` Straight: A New CSS Performance Diagnostics Snippet]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/css-head-tag/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/css-head-tag/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We love little useful tools and techniques to help folks get their work done better and faster. Today, we’d love to shine the spotlights on a little helper that helps spot common performance bottlenecks easily: [ct.css](https://csswizardry.com/ct/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build Your Own Mouseless Development Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/mouseless-development-environment/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/mouseless-development-environment/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a development environment with the shell as a keystone offers multiple benefits. You can customize everything depending on your own needs, and the biggest of all, you can control your entire development environment with your keyboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthieu Cneude)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Web Development Tools Are Helping Users Keep Pace With Rapid Change]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-development-tools-users-keep-pace-rapid-change/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-development-tools-users-keep-pace-rapid-change/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last 18 months have been a time of unprecedented turbulence. As the people of the world have flooded online, businesses have joined them, using web development tools to adapt in real-time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Imposter Domains Re-Publishing Your Website?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/imposter-domains-republishing-website/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/imposter-domains-republishing-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content scraping is a fact of life on the Internet. When you think of web scraping, you probably do not think about the scrapers turning around and immediately serving your entire, whole page content on another website. But what if your site content is being re-published?  It might be already happening.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ken Harker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monetize Open-Source Software With Gatsby Functions And Stripe]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/monetize-open-source-software-gatsby-functions-stripe/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/monetize-open-source-software-gatsby-functions-stripe/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Functions provide front-end developers a way to write and use server-side code without the hassle of maintaining a server. If making money from open-source is of interest to you and your site isn’t built using Gatsby, this approach may well be the answer you were looking for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Quality Assurance: From User Requirements To Web Risk Management]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/journey-into-web-quality-assurance/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/journey-into-web-quality-assurance/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twenty years ago, Elie Sloïm chose to dedicate his professional life to web quality assurance. He started asking, ”What does quality mean for a web user?” Well, this article explains everything he has learned along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Elie Sloïm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reasons To Build A CRM-Powered Website For Your Business]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reasons-build-crm-powered-website-business/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reasons-build-crm-powered-website-business/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating a CRM with your business website has numerous benefits. In this article, Zara Cooper explains what these benefits are and why websites should be integrated with a CRM platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.1"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T06:39:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Unexpected nested element in author field crashes the parser
Thank you @ad-m]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing The Need For Pseudo-Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reducing-need-pseudo-elements/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reducing-need-pseudo-elements/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, pseudo-elements have faithfully helped front-end developers implement creative designs. While they still have an important place, we can now leave pseudo-elements behind in some scenarios, thanks to newer CSS properties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcel Moreau)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Power Of Pen And Paper Sketching]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/power-pen-paper-sketching/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/power-pen-paper-sketching/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing for digital spaces, it’s natural to default to digital mockup tools, but doing so cuts out a world of possibilities. Analog drawing can unleash your imagination and allow you to focus on what’s most important at the start: the ideas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tracy Osborn)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orchestrating Complexity With Web Animations API]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/orchestrating-complexity-web-animations-api/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/orchestrating-complexity-web-animations-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are way too many options in Web Animations API to pick them up that easily. Learning how timing works and how to control the playback of several animations at once makes for a solid foundation on which to base your projects on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kirill Myshkin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: Excellent Editorial]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-design-done-well-excellent-editorial/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-design-done-well-excellent-editorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They say content is king, and they’re right. The web has unlocked untold possibilities for storytellers — provided the story is right, of course. Here are some of our favorite examples of editorial content thriving in the digital realm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using SWR React Hooks With Next.js’ Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/useswr-react-hook-library-incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/useswr-react-hook-library-incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When paired with ISR and Next.js’ API routes, SWR can be used to create a responsive user experience. In this article, Sam Poder explains what SWR is, where to use it (and where not), and how to build a website by using Incremental Static Regeneration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sam Poder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Decisions For Building Flexible Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/developer-decisions-building-flexible-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/developer-decisions-building-flexible-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll walk through the process of taking a seemingly simple design for a text-and-media component and deciding how best to translate it into code, keeping in mind the needs of both users and content authors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Smashing Online Workshops on Front-End & UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/new-smashing-online-workshops-sep-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/new-smashing-online-workshops-sep-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the state of HTML Email, Vue.js and Next.js? What are new, smart interface design patterns we could use? Let’s figure it out. With our brand new online workshops on front-end & design. Now with **free workshops** for you to test the waters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New With DevTools: Cross-Browser Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/devtools-cross-browser-edition/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/devtools-cross-browser-edition/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what’s new with developer tools in Firefox, Edge, Chrome and Safari. Discover new and powerful features that will help you be more comfortable and productive when testing and debugging across browsers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Patrick Brosset)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP/3: Practical Deployment Options (Part 3)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/http3-practical-deployment-options-part3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/http3-practical-deployment-options-part3/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After almost five years in development, the new HTTP/3 protocol is nearing its final form. Let’s take a close look at the challenges involved in deploying and testing HTTP/3, and how and if you should change your websites and resources as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Robin Marx)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing Carbon Emissions On The Web]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reducing-carbon-emissions-on-web/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reducing-carbon-emissions-on-web/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-03T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Websites, unfortunately, aren’t as environmentally friendly as we might like them to be. This article contains some thoughts and experiences from trying to clean them up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Berwyn Powell)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive Learning Tools For Front-End Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/interactive-learning-tools-front-end-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/interactive-learning-tools-front-end-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive coding tools to help you learn CSS, JavaScript, SQL, React, Vim, regular expressions and Jamstack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep Dive Into The Wonderful World Of SVG Displacement Filtering]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/deep-dive-wonderful-world-svg-displacement-filtering/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/deep-dive-wonderful-world-svg-displacement-filtering/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What exactly is a displacement filter? In this article, Dirk Weber explains the SVG `feDisplacementMap` filter primitive with a good number of examples to demonstrate the concept of animated displacement maps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dirk Weber)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State Management In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/state-management-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/state-management-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-31T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By combining some React APIs, we can accurately manage “simple” states. With Next.js though, we can quickly find situations where we need to accommodate many other requirements. Let’s have a look at some patterns to accomplish all that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>