<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-10-23T00:45:44.976Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-10-23T00:45:44.976Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vue vs React – How to Go from One Framework to the Other]]></title>
        <id>6130bf69d6679a07b7d40a74</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vue-vs-react-comparison-of-frameworks/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-22T21:59:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, a new trending front-end framework is released every now and then. But React and Vue.js still stand as the most popular among all the other alternatives.  And although both are performant, elegant, and arguably easy to learn, they have some different opinions on how certain things should]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Include (a Certain HTML element within another Certain HTML Element)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354567</id>
        <link href="https://caninclude.glitch.me/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-22T17:57:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A single-serving website from Alexander Vishnyakov for testing if it’s valid to put any particular HTML element within another type of HTML element. Kinda neat to have a quick reference for this.
Some combinations feel fairly obvious: can you put …
The post Can Include (a Certain HTML element within another Certain HTML Element) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the CSS Paint API: Rounding Shapes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353391</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/exploring-the-css-paint-api-rounding-shapes/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-22T14:02:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adding borders to complex shapes is a pain, but rounding the corner of complex shapes is a nightmare! Luckily, the CSS Paint API is here to the rescue! That’s what we’re going to look at as part of this “Exploring …
The post Exploring the CSS Paint API: Rounding Shapes appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Real-Time Multi-User Game From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/real-time-multi-user-game/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/real-time-multi-user-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-22T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article highlights the process, technical decisions and lessons learned behind building the real-time game Autowuzzler. Learn how to share game state across multiple clients in real-time with Colyseus, do physics calculations with Matter.js, store data in Supabase.io and build the front-end with SvelteKit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Martin Grubinger)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What if… you could use Visual Studio Code as the editor of in-browser Developer Tools?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354537</id>
        <link href="https://christianheilmann.com/2021/10/12/what-if-you-could-use-visual-studio-code-as-the-editor-of-in-browser-developer-tools/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T22:14:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not uncommon for my front-end workflow to go something like this:
Work on thing.
See that thing in an automatically refreshed browser.
See something wrong with that thing.
Inspect and correct the thing in DevTools.
Apply the correct code 
…
The post What if… you could use Visual Studio Code as the editor of in-browser Developer Tools? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS-in-React Landscape]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353318</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-css-in-react-landscape/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T22:13:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
I only half-jokingly refer to the CSS-in-JS world as CSS-in-React. Many of the libraries listed below theoretically work in non-React situations — they generally call that “framework-agnostic”) — but I’d guess the vast majority …
The post The CSS-in-React Landscape appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dotfiles – What is a Dotfile and How to Create it in Mac and Linux]]></title>
        <id>616fed81d48e1707b6d7898e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dotfiles-what-is-a-dot-file-and-how-to-create-it-in-mac-and-linux/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T19:49:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dotfiles are important files that will play an integral role in your career as a software developer.  First, they can help make you more productive. But not only that - you'll be able to have that productive setup you created for youself on any machine.  This article is an introduction]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code an Endless Runner Game Using Unreal Engine and C++]]></title>
        <id>6171b7b2d48e1707b6d79998</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-an-endless-runner-game-using-unreal-engine-and-c/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T19:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Endless runner games can be fun and addicting. Also, an endless runner game is a great game development project for a beginner. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create an endless runner game using Unreal Engine and C++. Fahir]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is msmpeng.exe? Why is it High CPU Disk Usage?]]></title>
        <id>617144ced48e1707b6d79686</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-msmpeng-exe-why-is-it-of-high-cpu-disk-usage/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T15:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[msmpeng.exe is an important part of Windows Security, formerly known as Windows Defender. It scans your computer for various threats ranging from malware to spyware, then renders the appropriate solution(s).  In this article, I will take you through what mempeng.exe is, the reason why it eats up]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Contact Form With Next.js and Netlify]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353128</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-create-a-contact-form-with-next-js-and-netlify/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T14:26:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re going to create a contact form with Next.js and Netlify that displays a confirmation screen and features enhanced spam detection.
Next.js is a powerful React framework for developing performant React applications that scale. By integrating a Next.js site with …
The post How to Create a Contact Form With Next.js and Netlify appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Monica Powell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Respecting Users’ Motion Preferences]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/respecting-users-motion-preferences/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/respecting-users-motion-preferences/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The `prefers-reduced-motion` media query has excellent support in all modern browsers going back a couple of years. In this article, Michelle Barker explains why there’s no reason not to use it today to make your sites more accessible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Adapter Design Pattern in React]]></title>
        <id>617058f3d48e1707b6d7913d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/adapter-design-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T00:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're coding in React or any other tool, you might want or need to use a third-party library. Let's talk about an approach which will ensure that the third-party libraries you use will blend well with your application. As application developers, there's no need to reinvent the wheel every]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Typography Links VIII]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353866</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-typography-links-viii/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-20T23:25:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you know what to use the @ sign for something other than email addresses and Twitter handles? I do! —  Pawel Grzybek notes how some old physical typewriters had an “Arroba” on them which was represented with the @ 
…
The post Some Typography Links VIII appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Angular - Crash Course]]></title>
        <id>61708409d48e1707b6d79387</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-angular-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-20T21:07:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular is a TypeScript-based free and open-source web application framework created by Google. We just published a 2-hour Angular crash course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Slobodan Gajic created this course. Slobodan has created a bunch of amazing courses on his own channel. In this course you will learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Safe Area Context in React Native Apps to Avoid the Notch]]></title>
        <id>616945f580d82d07c45a5160</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-safe-area-context-to-avoid-notches-in-react-native-apps/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-20T19:37:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most devices nowadays come with a notch at the top of the screen. So when you're building a mobile application using React Native, you need to make sure that the content of the app's screen is rendered correctly across different types of devices. In this article, we'll look at two]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is my IP Address for my Router? How to Find your Wifi Address]]></title>
        <id>616ffc6dd48e1707b6d78992</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-my-ip-address-for-my-router-how-to-find-your-wifi-address/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-20T19:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you might need to know your router’s IP address. This will give you access to the setup page so you can make configuration changes like changing passwords, kicking out unwanted users, limiting users, and so on.  In this article, I will show you how to find out what]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Your Own Bragdoc With Eleventy]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353638</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-your-own-bragdoc-with-eleventy/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-20T15:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter what stage you’re at as a developer, the tasks we complete—whether big or small—make a huge impact in our personal and professional growth. Unfortunately, those tasks aren’t always recognized because they can easily get lost in the sea …
The post Creating Your Own Bragdoc With Eleventy appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Leung</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building The SSG I’ve Always Wanted: An 11ty, Vite And JAM Sandwich]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-ssg-11ty-vite-jam-sandwich/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-ssg-11ty-vite-jam-sandwich/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in January 2020, Ben Holmes set out to do what just about every web developer does each year: rebuild his personal site. In this article, he shares his story of how he set out to build his own build pipeline from absolute ground zero and created “Slinkity”.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Holmes)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[@supports selector()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354115</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/supports-selector/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T21:12:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I didn’t realize the support for @supports determining selector support was so good! I usually think of @supports as a way to test for property: value pair support. But with the selector() function, we can test for selector support …
The post @supports selector() appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GraphQL for Front End Developers]]></title>
        <id>616bcb8580d82d07c45a5deb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/graphql-for-front-end-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T17:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a front end developer who is new to the world of GraphQL and you're thinking about getting started with it, this article is for you.  In this article, we will explore GraphQL basics and kick start our journey with it by building a simple project.  What is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Binary Tree Algorithms in Technical Interviews]]></title>
        <id>616ef9b5d48e1707b6d78265</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-binary-tree-algorithms-in-technical-interviews/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T17:13:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A binary tree is a common data structure used in software development. It is also a frequent topic in technical coding interviews. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you all about binary tree algorithms and prepare you to use them in coding]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview With Elad Shechter on “The New CSS Reset”]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353462</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/an-interview-with-elad-shechter-on-the-new-css-reset/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T14:48:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey folks! Elad reached out to me to show me his new CSS reset project called the-new-css-reset. It’s quite interesting! I thought a neat way to share it with you is not only to point you toward it, but …
The post An Interview With Elad Shechter on “The New CSS Reset” appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elad Shechter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building An API With Gatsby Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-api-gatsby-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-api-gatsby-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, Paul Scanlon explains how to build an API by using Gatsby Functions and what you need to keep in mind when deploying it to Gatsby Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 42 With Jeff Smith: What Is DevOps?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/smashing-podcast-episode-42/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/smashing-podcast-episode-42/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about DevOps. What is it, and is it a string to add to your web development bow? Drew McLellan talks to expert Jeff Smith to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three-Digit Browser Versions in March 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354269</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/three-digit-browser-versions-in-march-2022/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-18T22:53:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We aren’t supposed to be doing any sort of decision-making based on browser User-Agent Strings. But, ya know, collectively, we do.
Karl Dubost notes that there is a significant change coming to them, notably moving the version integer past …
The post Three-Digit Browser Versions in March 2022 appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Nearly Headless WordPress Website]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353308</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-build-a-nearly-headless-wordpress-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-18T14:48:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I believe that a traditional WordPress theme should be able to work as effectively as a static site or a headless web app. The overwhelming majority of WordPress websites are built with a good ol’ fashioned WordPress theme. Most of …
The post How to Build a Nearly Headless WordPress Website appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Standiford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solving CLS Issues In A Next.js-Powered E-Commerce Website (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/nextjs-ecommerce-cls-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/nextjs-ecommerce-cls-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cumulative Layout Shift is one of the hardest core web vital to debug. In this article, we go through different tools to investigate CLS, when to use them(and when not), and solutions to some of the CLS issues we faced in our Next.js-based e-commerce website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Arijit Mondal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Simple But Effective Mental Health Routine For Programmers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/effective-mental-health-routine-programmers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/effective-mental-health-routine-programmers/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll look at why taking care of our work-life balance is important, how to develop a simple and effective mental health routine, and the most common and efficient techniques you can use to make your custom routine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dave Oscar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.3]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.3</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.3"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T00:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: broken links in documentation
Chore: Dependency updates
Thank you: @hirdot]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expandable Sections Within a CSS Grid]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353473</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/expandable-sections-within-a-css-grid/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T16:18:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love CSS Grid. I love how, with just a few lines of code, we can achieve fully responsive grid layouts, often without any media queries at all. I’m quite comfortable wrangling CSS Grid to produce interesting layouts, while keeping …
The post Expandable Sections Within a CSS Grid appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kev Bonett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tips And Tricks For Evaluating UX/UI Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/tips-tricks-evaluating-ux-ui-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/tips-tricks-evaluating-ux-ui-designers/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customers may start using your app because you offer a unique product, but user experience is what makes them stay. For that, you need excellent UX designers, and the know-how to spot them when hiring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nataliya Sambir)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Different Degrees of Custom Property Usage]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353057</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/different-degrees-of-custom-property-usage/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T14:35:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One way to work with Custom Properties is to think of them as design tokens. Colors, spacings, fonts, and whatnot. You set them at the root of the page and use them throughout your CSS. Very useful, and the classic …
The post Different Degrees of Custom Property Usage appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded Analytics Made Simple With Cumul.io Integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353243</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/embedded-analytics-made-simple-with-cumul-io-integrations/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T14:32:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
Browse through SaaS communities on Twitter, LinkedIn, Reddit, Discord, you name it and you’ll see a common theme appear in many of them. That theme can go by many names: BI, analytics, insights and …
The post Embedded Analytics Made Simple With Cumul.io Integrations appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cumul.io</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart CSS Solutions For Common UI Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/modern-css-solutions-for-common-problems/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/modern-css-solutions-for-common-problems/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing CSS has probably never been more fun and exciting than it is today. In this post we’ll take a look at common problems and use cases we all have to face in our work and how to solve them with modern CSS. If you’re interested, we’ve also just recently covered [CSS auditing tools](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-auditing-tools/), [CSS generators](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-generators/), [front-end boilerplates](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/) and [VS code extensions](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/) — you might find them useful, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bonsai Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353719</id>
        <link href="https://bonsaibrowser.com/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-13T22:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web-browser for research that helps programmers think clearly.
With Bonsai, rather than being like, I’m going to go use my web browser now, you hit Option + Space and it brings up a browser. It’s either full-screen or a …
The post Bonsai Browser appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming Live Workshops On Front-End & UX (Oct 2021&ndash;Jan 2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/new-smashing-online-workshops-oct-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/new-smashing-online-workshops-oct-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you like a good interface design challenge? What about accessibility testing and design systems? Or maybe Next.js and advanced CSS? With our new online workshops on front-end & design, we cover all of it. Ah, and [here's what our workshops are like](https://vimeo.com/616485526).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful React APIs For Building Flexible Components With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/react-apis-building-flexible-components-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/react-apis-building-flexible-components-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React with JSX is a fantastic tool for making easy-to-use components. Typescript components make it an absolute pleasure for developers to integrate your components into their apps and explore your APIs. Learn about three lesser-known React APIs that can take your components to the next level, and help you build even better React Components in this article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Gaurav Khanna)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bridging The Gap Between Designers And Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/bridging-gap-between-designers-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/bridging-gap-between-designers-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UXPin has recently launched a new feature called “Merge”. This tool aims to break through the chasms of design and development, all while improving the agility and quality our teams expect. This new technology may cause some rethink on how the whole design team and engineering team collaborates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthew Talebi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Autofill Dark Pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/autofill-dark-pattern/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/autofill-dark-pattern/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A “dark pattern” is a deceptive UX pattern that tricks users into doing things they may not really want to do. In this article, Alvaro Montoro does a little experiment to find out how much privacy is taken away from users across three different browsers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alvaro Montoro)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Composable CSS Animation In Vue With AnimXYZ]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/composable-css-animation-vue-animxyz/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/composable-css-animation-vue-animxyz/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most animation libraries like GSAP and Framer Motion are built purely with JavaScript or TypeScript, unlike AnimXYZ, which is labelled “the first composable CSS animation toolkit”, built mainly with SCSS While a simple library, it can be used to achieve a lot of awesome animation on the web in a short amount of time and little code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ejiro Asiuwhu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Static-First MadLib Generator With Portable Text And Netlify On-Demand Builder Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/static-first-madlib-generator-portable-text-netlify-builder-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/static-first-madlib-generator-portable-text-netlify-builder-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be building an interactive fiction experience in which a user can insert words that match parts of speech given by the content creator. Let’s go!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Bryan Robinson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freebie: COVID-19 Icon Set (56 Icons, AI, EPS, SVG, PNG)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/freebie-coronavirus-icon-set/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/freebie-coronavirus-icon-set/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every once in a while, we publish [freebies](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/category/freebies/) related to different occasions and themes. We hope that with this icon set, every designer will be able to find their own use case and contribute to saving lives. Free for personal and commercial use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Anton Tyschenko)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To CSS Debugging]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/guide-debugging-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/guide-debugging-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging in CSS means figuring out what might be the problem when you have unexpected layout results. We’ll look at a few categories bugs often fit into, see how we can evaluate the situation, and explore techniques that help prevent these bugs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local Testing A Serverless API (API Gateway And Lambda)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/local-testing-serverless-api-gateway-lambda/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/local-testing-serverless-api-gateway-lambda/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever struggled with testing cloud services locally? Specifically, have you ever struggled with locally testing an API that uses API Gateway and Lambda, with the Serverless framework, on AWS? In this article, Tom Hudson shares a quick overview of how easy it is to quickly set up your project to test locally before deploying to AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tom Hudson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An Expandable Accessible Gallery]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/build-expandable-accessible-gallery/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/build-expandable-accessible-gallery/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be looking at how to set up a gallery that is expandable as well as accessible with a few tips and tricks along the way. Let’s get started!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Silvestar Bistrović)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Search Functionality In Your Nuxt App Using Algolia InstantSearch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/search-functionality-nuxt-app-algolia-instantsearch/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/search-functionality-nuxt-app-algolia-instantsearch/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many websites have some sort of search feature because it helps users navigate through their content easily. Implementing it the right way can be tricky and might not give a good user experience. In this tutorial, we will be integrating Algolia, a popular and powerful search service for the best experience on our Nuxt site.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Miracle Onyenma)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Time Of Transition (October 2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-30T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get your desktop ready for fall and the upcoming Halloween season with a fresh batch of desktop wallpapers. Created with love by designers and artists from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for October 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Modern Image Formats: AVIF And WebP]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/modern-image-formats-avif-webp/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/modern-image-formats-avif-webp/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T08:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll highlight how modern image formats (AVIF or WebP) can improve compression by up to 50% and deliver better quality per-byte while still looking visually appealing. We’ll compare what’s possible at high-quality, low-quality and file-size targets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Accessibility Of Your Markdown]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/improving-accessibility-of-markdown/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/improving-accessibility-of-markdown/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can find Markdown in many places on the Internet. This article covers different aspects of Markdown and how it interacts with other technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Dive Into Cypress For End-to-End Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/cypress-end-to-end-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/cypress-end-to-end-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is end-to-end testing a painful topic for you? In this article, Ramona Schwering explains how to handle end-to-end testing with Cypress and make it make it not so tedious and expensive for yourself, but fun instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ramona Schwering)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.2"/>
        <updated>2021-09-26T18:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: unicode characters in URL caused download error
Fixed: project root npm install error
Added: unit test library
Chore: Dependency updates
Thank you: @CaptNo1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rebuilding A Large E-Commerce Website With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/lessons-learned-ecommerce-nextjs-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/lessons-learned-ecommerce-nextjs-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We made the switch from a more traditional integrated e-commerce platform to a headless platform with Next.js. Here are the most important lessons learned while rebuilding a large e-commerce site with Next.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jonne Kats)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Online Workshop: Frustrating Design Patterns And How To Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/smashing-workshop-frustrating-design-patterns/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/smashing-workshop-frustrating-design-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T06:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve seen them before. Confusing and frustrating design patterns that seem to be chasing you everywhere you go, from one website to another. It’s time to fix them for good in a [free Smashing online workshop](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/workshops/vitaly-friedman-frustrating-patterns/) next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>