<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-11-29T00:42:41.633Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-11-29T00:42:41.633Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When is it “Right” to Reach for  contain and will-change in CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357271</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/when-is-it-right-to-reach-for-contain-and-will-change-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T20:43:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve got some blind spots in CSS-related performance things. One example is the will-change property. It’s a good name. You’re telling the browser some particular property (or the scroll-position or content) uh, will, change:
.el {
  will-change: opacity;

…
The post When is it “Right” to Reach for  contain and will-change in CSS? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Handy Little System for Animated Entrances in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357239</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-handy-little-system-for-animated-entrances-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T16:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love little touches that make a website feel like more than just a static document. What if web content wouldn’t just “appear” when a page loaded, but instead popped, slid, faded, or spun into place? It might be a …
The post A Handy Little System for Animated Entrances in CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neale Van Fleet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Maintain A Large Next.js Application]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/maintain-large-nextjs-application/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/maintain-large-nextjs-application/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Nirmalya discusses some of the complex problems that he faced while building and maintaining large Next.js applications. He always explains how these problems can be solved by using various tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nirmalya Ghosh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Websocket Real Time Communication to Your SaaS App]]></title>
        <id>619ba16011d3cb08287aa2ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-websocket-real-time-communication-to-your-saas-app/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T23:50:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this conference talk made for Tech Fest 2021, Steven Lemmo talks to you about building SaaS Applications with WebSockets. Here is a full breakdown of what he will cover in this 40 minute talk: The reason for this talkWhy Websockets?Websockets minimal API exampleRest Web ServicesMultiple ListenersFull DuplexWebsockets time-lineTypeScriptVendor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Color Shades – Hex Code and RGB for Gray Color Palette]]></title>
        <id>619bcc5611d3cb08287aa66f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/color-shades-hex-code-and-rgb-for-gray-color-palette/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T23:47:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colors play an integral role in how usable and accessible your web design projects are.  At times, they can even make or break a project.  Having a color palette comprised of different shades and hues of a specific color can be really helpful. It helps you visualize how you can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Analysis with Python for Excel Users Course]]></title>
        <id>619e979225888a07c3e1b545</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-analysis-with-python-for-excel-users-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T20:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you know how to use Microsoft Excel and want to learn how to do data analysis with Python? You are in luck. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to do Data Analysis with Python. This course will be especially]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Won&#x27;t My Computer Connect to My Hotspot? [Fixed on Windows 10 PC WiFi]]]></title>
        <id>619e3cdd25888a07c3e1b16d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-wont-my-computer-connect-to-my-hotspot-fixed-on-windows-10-pc-wifi/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T18:44:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A mobile hotspot is a quick and efficient way to share an internet connection with other devices like computers, iPads, or other mobile phones.  A hotspot is also a good alternative to WiFi – especially if the WiFi in your area is unbearably slow or won't connect.  Sometimes, you might experience]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I Learned from The Pragmatic Programmer and The Clean Coder]]></title>
        <id>619c873711d3cb08287aaf76</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/lessons-learned-from-the-pragmatic-programmer-and-the-clean-coder/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T16:38:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently finished reading The Pragmatic Programmer 20th Anniversary Edition (2019) and The Clean Coder (2011). You'll find these books on almost every “top 10 Software Development books” list out there.  My goal was to learn, improve, and get the kind of knowledge that a teacher from mine used to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Generative Patterns with The CSS Paint API]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357294</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-generative-patterns-with-the-css-paint-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T15:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The browser has long been a medium for art and design. From Lynn Fisher’s joyful A Single Div creations to Diana Smith’s staggeringly detailed CSS paintings, wildly creative, highly skilled developers have — over the years — continuously pushed …
The post Creating Generative Patterns with The CSS Paint API appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Francis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why and How to Add Feature Toggles to Your Software]]></title>
        <id>619e8cba25888a07c3e1b499</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-and-how-to-add-feature-toggles-to-your-software/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T15:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feature Toggles (aka Feature Flags) are a technique used in software development in order to hide, enable or disable a particular feature during runtime. They allow teams to modify system behavior without changing code. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp YouTube channel that will teach you why and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[D3.js Tutorial – Data Visualization for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>618ed39211d3cb08287a5535</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/d3js-tutorial-data-visualization-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T15:03:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'm going to walk you through how to use D3.js in a step by step and beginner-friendly way. We'll talk about what D3.js is, how it works, and we'll create some basic visualizations to add transitions, interactions, and zooming. Table of Contents Getting Started  What]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Ember – Ember.js Tips for Beginners Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>619cdd9d11d3cb08287ab09c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-ember-ember-js-tips-for-beginners-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T15:02:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this talk, Designer turned Software Developer Lenora Porter talks about her journey learning Ember.js. She also shares her tips for beginners who are about to start their journey. Here are her top 4 take-aways: How to Learn Ember.jsHave the Mindset of a BeginnerThis is the foundational work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Showcase Of Lovely Little Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/showcase-lovely-little-websites/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/showcase-lovely-little-websites/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instead of spending your coffee break scrolling through your social feeds, how about a lovely little website instead? We came across some fantastic ones that are just too good not to be shared. But be warned, your break might take a bit longer than intended.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All the Math You Need to Know in Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>6197c7ce11d3cb08287a9271</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/all-the-math-you-need-in-artificial-intelligence/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T00:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m an AI researcher, and I’ve received quite a few emails asking me just how much math is required in Artificial Intelligence. I won’t lie: it’s a lot of math. And this is one of the reasons AI puts off many beginners. After much research and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is GitOps? Principles, Best Practices, and Kubernetes Workflow]]></title>
        <id>619bb55911d3cb08287aa581</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gitops-principles-kubernetes-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T22:50:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this talk, CTO Cornelia Davis will teach you what GitOps is and what its four main principles are.  What is GitOps?The first thing you need to know is that GitOps is a set of modern best practises for deploying and managing cloud native infrastructure and applications.  And it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which SVG technique performs best for way too many icons?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357412</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/which-svg-technique-performs-best-for-way-too-many-icons/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T19:21:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tyler Sticka digs in here in the best possible way: by making a test page and literally measuring performance. Maybe 1,000 icons is a little bit of an edge case, but hey, 250 rows of data with four icons in …
The post Which SVG technique performs best for way too many icons? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Control Layout in a Multi-Directional Website]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356977</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/control-layout-in-a-multi-directional-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T16:06:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many business websites need a multilingual setup. As with anything development-related, implementing one in an easy, efficient, and maintainable way is desirable. Designing and developing to be ready for multiple languages, whether it happens right at launch or is expected …
The post Control Layout in a Multi-Directional Website appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alaa Abd El-Rahim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding A Dyslexia-Friendly Mode To A Website]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dyslexia-friendly-mode-website/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dyslexia-friendly-mode-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a little CSS, we can adapt our web designs to be more accommodating for people with dyslexia. In this article, we’ll explore those techniques by adding a dyslexia-friendly mode to an existing design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (John C Barstow)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On User Tracking and Industry Standards on Privacy]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357149</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/on-user-tracking-and-industry-standards-on-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T21:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inspired by Eva PenzeyMoog’s new book, Jeremy highlights the widespread user tracking situation in this industry:
There was a line that really stood out to me: 
The idea that it’s alright to do whatever unethical thing is currently the 
…
The post On User Tracking and Industry Standards on Privacy appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS “decorations”]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357046</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-decorations/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T18:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A reader wrote to me the other day asking about this bit of CSS they came across in Wikipedia’s Common.css:
.mw-collapsible-leftside-toggle .mw-collapsible-toggle {
  /* @noflip */
  float: left;
  /* @noflip */
  text-align: left;
}
What’s that @noflip business? That’s …
The post CSS “decorations” appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Workshops: Winter 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashingconf-workshops-winter-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashingconf-workshops-winter-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the state of CSS, Vue.js and Next.js? What are new, smart interface design patterns we could use? Let’s figure it out. With our [online workshops on UX, front-end and design](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsive Layouts, Fewer Media Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357080</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/responsive-layouts-fewer-media-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T15:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We cannot talk about web development without talking about Responsive Design. It’s just a given these days and has been for many years. Media queries are a part of Responsive Design and they aren’t going anywhere. Since the introduction of …
The post Responsive Layouts, Fewer Media Queries appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of Wix Websites (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/improving-performance-wix-websites-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/improving-performance-wix-websites-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing a performance culture is very important. In this article, Dan Shappir shares which actions and processes the Wix team put in place in order to achieve dramatic improvements in the performance of websites built and hosted on their platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dan Shappir)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reimagine Atomic CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357234</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/reimagine-atomic-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T22:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not the biggest fan of Atomic CSS myself. I don’t like all the classes. I like to express my styles in CSS because I find CSS… good. But I appreciate that a lot of people seem to like it, …
The post Reimagine Atomic CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coding Font Game]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357227</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/coding-font-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T21:18:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A tournament bracket UI where you pick your favorite between two coding fonts and your choices are whittled down all the way to a final winner. A clever way to suss out your own taste and arrive at a choice.…
The post Coding Font Game appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallax Powered by CSS Custom Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357192</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/parallax-powered-by-css-custom-properties/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T15:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good friend Kent C. Dodds has recently dropped his new website which had a lot of work go into it. I was fortunate enough that Kent reached out a while back and asked if I could come up with some …
The post Parallax Powered by CSS Custom Properties appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jhey Tompkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js Wildcard Subdomains]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/nextjs-wildcard-subdomains/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/nextjs-wildcard-subdomains/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hosting with a wildcard subdomain enables your users to visit your site on any subdomain of your domain (*.example.com), and as you can imagine, we can use this to create unique user experiences which we’ll be exploring in this article through a Next.js lens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sam Poder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Many Faces of VS Code in the Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356818</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-many-faces-of-vs-code-in-the-browser/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T20:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code is built from web technologies (HTML, CSS, and JavaScript), but dare I say today it’s mostly used a local app that’s installed on your machine. That’s starting to shift, though, as there has been an absolute explosion of …
The post The Many Faces of VS Code in the Browser appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Date and Time Recipes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356570</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/php-date-and-time-recipes/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T15:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with dates and times is one of those things that can frustrate programmers a lot. At the same time, they are fundamental to software development, used from everything from meta and how things are ordered to time-based triggers and …
The post PHP Date and Time Recipes appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arjuna Sky Kok</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Trickery Custom Radios and Checkboxes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356895</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/zero-trickery-custom-radios-and-checkboxes/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T00:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I feel like half of all “custom-designed radio buttons and checkboxes” do two things:
Make them bigger
Colorize them
I always think of SurveyMonkey for having big chunky radios and checkboxes. And indeed, just poking at their interface quickly, even …
The post Zero Trickery Custom Radios and Checkboxes appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What do you get for using a search input type?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356885</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-do-you-get-for-using-a-search-input-type/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T23:09:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like this: <input type="search">
You get an extra-round-y appearance in Safari, which at one time matched the macOS look for search inputs, but not really anymore. I don’t hate the look, except…
Safari totally ignores the font-size you set on 
…
The post What do you get for using a search input type? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Modern CSS Colors With RGB, HSL, HWB, LAB And LCH]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/guide-modern-css-colors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/guide-modern-css-colors/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll take a look at the best ways to handle colors in CSS today, some tips for using them in a design system, and what we can expect from our colors in the not-too-distant future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Touch Design For Mobile Interfaces, A New Smashing Book By Steven Hoober]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/touch-design-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/touch-design-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Touch Design for Mobile Interfaces”, our brand-new guide on designing for mobile with proven, universal, human-centric standards. 400 pages. Shipping starting in early January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powerful Terminal And Command-Line (CLI) Tools For Modern Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/powerful-terminal-commandline-tools-modern-web-development/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/powerful-terminal-commandline-tools-modern-web-development/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s your favorite command-line tool? In this post, Louis Lazaris shares a collection of relevant command-line apps and utilities that he has personally come across in the past few years. If there’s a useful one that hasn’t been mentioned and one you use regularly, please do share it in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful React Hooks That You Can Use In Your Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/useful-react-hooks/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/useful-react-hooks/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The React team introduced several hooks in React 16.8 which you can use from third-party providers in your application, or even create your own custom hook. In this tutorial, we’ll take a look at some of the most useful hooks in React and how to use them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ifeanyi Dike)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Good To Great In Dashboard Design: Research, Decluttering And Data Viz]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dashboard-design-research-decluttering-data-viz/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dashboard-design-research-decluttering-data-viz/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dribbbleshots just might be the hotbed of questionable dashboards. Striking visuals, little context, and no research: all recipes for mediocrity. Mediocrity won’t do. We’ll pursue greatness. And in that pursuit, we’ll cover research, decluttering, and data visualization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adam Fard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Localizing Your Next.js App]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/localizing-your-nextjs-app/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/localizing-your-nextjs-app/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Internationalized routing is not exactly a new feature on Next.js. In this article, we are not only checking what we get from this feature, but also how to leverage such functionalities to achieve the best user experience and a smooth developer experience as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatically Transforming And Optimizing Images And Videos On Your WordPress Website]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/transforming-optimizing-images-videos-wordpress-website/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/transforming-optimizing-images-videos-wordpress-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Leonardo Losoviz explains how Cloudinary’s integration can be used with WordPress to produce and deliver optimal digital experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Hydrogen: A React Framework For Dynamic, Contextual And Personalized E-Commerce]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/hydrogen-react-framework-dynamic-contextual-personalized-ecommerce/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/hydrogen-react-framework-dynamic-contextual-personalized-ecommerce/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A great commerce experience is not a Lighthouse score or a set of Core Web Vitals figures (although both are important inputs), but it’s also a trilemma that carefully balances competing needs of delivering a great customer experience, dynamic storefront capabilities and long-term business objectives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ilya Grigorik)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Value Of Concept Testing As Part Of Product Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/concept-testing-part-of-product-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/concept-testing-part-of-product-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concept testing ideas before moving into a detailed design is good UX practice. In this article, Victor Yocco presents details on how and when to engage in concept testing, as well as case studies providing details on the insights gained in two very different settings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Yocco)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 43 With Matthew Phillips: What Is Astro?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashing-podcast-episode-43/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashing-podcast-episode-43/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about Astro. Will this modern static site builder launch you into the stratosphere? Drew McLellan talks to developer Matthew Phillips to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GraphQL On The Front-End (React And Apollo)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/graphql-frontend-react-apollo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/graphql-frontend-react-apollo/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Within the last decade, technologies like GraphQL have changed how we build web apps and how they communicate with each other. GraphQL provides certain benefits over REST APIs — let’s find out what they are.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (David Atanda)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep Dive Into Serverless UI With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/deep-dive-into-serverless-ui-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/deep-dive-into-serverless-ui-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless UI is simply a free, open-source command-line utility for quickly building and deploying serverless applications on the AWS platform. In this article, we will learn and cover everything needed on using Serverless UI to deploy our projects or serverless applications to cloud services providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ikeh Akinyemi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A Magento PWA: Customizing Themes vs. Coding From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/magento-pwa-customizing-themes-coding/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/magento-pwa-customizing-themes-coding/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article sheds the spotlight on Magento PWAs and explains why business owners are getting them (often instead of native applications). Alex Husar introduces ways of how progressive web applications can be developed on Magento, as well as go over the major pros and cons of each development path.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alex Husar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Splash Of Color For Misty Days (November 2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November is just around the corner, and with it, a new collection of desktop wallpapers to celebrate the beginning of the month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Let’s make November colorful!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>