<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-10-06T00:44:54.910Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-10-06T00:44:54.910Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scroll Shadows With JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352754</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/scroll-shadows-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T22:40:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scroll shadows are when you can see a little inset shadow on elements if (and only if) you can scroll in that direction. It’s just good UX. You can actually pull it off in CSS, which I think is …
The post Scroll Shadows With JavaScript appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conditional Border Radius In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353261</id>
        <link href="https://ishadeed.com/article/conditional-border-radius/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T19:18:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahmad Shadeed documents a bonafide CSS trick from the Facebook CSS codebase. The idea is that when an element is the full width of the viewport, it doesn’t have any border-radius. But otherwise, it has 8px of border-radius. …
The post Conditional Border Radius In CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Callback Function –Explained in Plain English]]></title>
        <id>61533caa64aefe07d3fa041a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-callback-function-plain-english/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T17:17:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every JavaScript beginner will face this question at least once: "What is a callback function?"  Well, we can find the answer in the word callback itself. It's all about notifying the caller after the successful completion or failure of a task.  In this article, I'll focus less on the technical]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Evolution of Tokenization – Byte Pair Encoding in NLP]]></title>
        <id>6159b85c4aa03507d94123fb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/evolution-of-tokenization/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T15:26:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Natural Language Processing may have come a little late to the AI game, but companies like Google and OpenAI are working wonders with NLP techniques these days. These companies have released state-of-the-art language models like BERT and GPT-2 and GPT-3. And GitHub Copilot and OpenAI codex are among some of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Branching Strategies in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352508</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/branching-strategies-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T14:28:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I'm going to talk about branching strategies and different types of Git branches. I’m also going to introduce you to two common branching workflows: Git Flow and GitHub Flow.
The post Branching Strategies in Git appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tobias Günther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ct.css — Performance Hints via Injected Stylesheet Alone]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353225</id>
        <link href="https://csswizardry.com/ct/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T14:28:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is some bonafide CSS trickery from Harry that gives you some generic performance advice based on what it sees in your <head> element. 
First, it’s possible to make a <style> block visible like any other element by changing the …
The post ct.css — Performance Hints via Injected Stylesheet Alone appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform Associate Certification Study Course – Pass the Exam With This Free 12+ Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>615b198b4aa03507d9412b36</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hashicorp-terraform-associate-certification-study-course-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-12-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T14:07:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to pass the HashiCorp Terraform Associate Certification with this free 12-hour course. What is the HashiCorp Terraform Associate?HashiCorp is a company specializing in open-source tools for multi-cloud workloads. HashiCorp's most popular tool is Terraform, which allows DevOps Engineers to write code to provision infrastructure for multiple Cloud]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local Testing A Serverless API (API Gateway And Lambda)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/local-testing-serverless-api-gateway-lambda/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/local-testing-serverless-api-gateway-lambda/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever struggled with testing cloud services locally? Specifically, have you ever struggled with locally testing an API that uses API Gateway and Lambda, with the Serverless framework, on AWS? In this article, Tom Hudson shares a quick overview of how easy it is to quickly set up your project to test locally before deploying to AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tom Hudson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Traceroute and Ping Commands to Troubleshoot Network Connectivity Issues]]></title>
        <id>5fff3ec998be260817e495ee</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/traceroute-and-ping/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-04T23:46:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ping and traceroute are common commands you can use to troubleshoot network problems.  Ping is a simple command that can test the reachability of a device on the network.  Traceroute is a command you use to 'trace' the route that a packet takes when traveling to its destination. It's useful]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your Own Developer Portfolio Website with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>6154775964aefe07d3fa0b7d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-developer-portfolio-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-04T20:59:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone needs websites and web applications these days. So there are many opportunities for you if you work as a web developer.  But if you want to get a web developer job, you'll need a good portfolio website to showcase your skills and experience.  In this tutorial, I'll discuss some]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickly Testing CSS Fallbacks]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353179</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/quickly-testing-css-fallbacks/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-04T19:15:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dumb trick alert! 
Not all browsers support all features. Say you want to write a fallback for browsers that doesn’t support CSS Grid. Not very common these days, but it’s just to illustrate a point.
You could write the supporting …
The post Quickly Testing CSS Fallbacks appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the OSI Model? Computer Networking for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>613b97f1852f4307d372b637</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/osi-model-computer-networking-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-04T16:27:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn about the core concepts of the Open Systems Interconnections (OSI) model in a simple and easy way. As a developer, it's a good idea to learn how things work "under the hood". That way you understand what your code and the tools you use]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is UX Design? User Experience Design Explained in Plain English]]></title>
        <id>61063c1d3306a507d1bfbfca</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/user-experience-design-what-does-a-ux-designer-do/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-04T16:21:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might have heard of the term User Experience or UX design. But what does it mean exactly? In this article, I will explain what UX design is and talk about how to become a UX designer.  What is UX design?The term User Experience refers to how users interact]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animation Techniques for Adding and Removing Items From a Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352819</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/animation-techniques-for-adding-and-removing-items-from-a-stack/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-04T14:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animating elements with CSS can either be quite easy or quite difficult depending on what you are trying to do. Changing the background color of a button when you hover over it? Easy. Animating the position and size of an …
The post Animation Techniques for Adding and Removing Items From a Stack appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Courtney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ShopTalk Goes Video]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352857</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/shoptalk-goes-video/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-04T14:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dave and I slapped up a little videos section of the ShopTalk website. Twelve so far! They are short-ish, between 10-20 minutes, each focused on one fairly specific thing. We’re kinda just dipping our toes here — we don’t …
The post ShopTalk Goes Video appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An Expandable Accessible Gallery]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/build-expandable-accessible-gallery/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/build-expandable-accessible-gallery/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be looking at how to set up a gallery that is expandable as well as accessible with a few tips and tricks along the way. Let’s get started!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Silvestar Bistrović)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 250 Best Free Online Courses of All Time – A Data-Driven Analysis [2021 Edition]]]></title>
        <id>5f9c98a3740569d1a4ca1b33</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-online-courses/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-03T04:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every year Class Central releases a list of the Best Free Online Courses Of All Time, based on tens of thousands of user reviews. This year, thanks to a growing number of reviews, I've expanded the list from 200 to 250 courses. For close to ten years, well-known and well-respected]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links on React and JavaScript II]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352717</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/links-on-react-and-javascript-ii/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-01T21:09:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use The Vite Build Tool with React — Vite is hot, in part, because it’s based on esbuild and wickedly fast. It’s from Evan You of Vue fame, but it’s not a Vue-specific tool. Here, NARUHODO covers how 
…
The post Links on React and JavaScript II appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using the platform]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352867</id>
        <link href="https://elisehe.in/2021/08/22/using-the-platform"/>
        <updated>2021-10-01T18:50:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm certainly not dogmatic about it, but I think if you can pull of a project with literally zero build process, it feels good while working on it and feels very good when you come back to it months/years later and can just pick up and go.
The post Using the platform appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Solve the Problem of Multiple Inheritance in Java]]></title>
        <id>613f8a73852f4307d372cc55</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-solve-multiple-inheritance-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-01T14:42:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Java is one of the most popular object-oriented programming languages in use today.  Because it is platform-independent, you will find Java applications on every type of device and every operating system. And because Java is relatively easy to learn, it is one of the first languages that many programmers pick]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Working With Built-in GraphQL Directives]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352798</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/working-with-built-in-graphql-directives/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-01T14:35:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Directives are one of GraphQL’s best — and most unspoken — features.
Let’s explore working with GraphQL’s built-in schema and operation directives that all GraphQL spec compliant APIs must implement. They are extremely useful if you are working with a …
The post Working With Built-in GraphQL Directives appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Barton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Search Functionality In Your Nuxt App Using Algolia InstantSearch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/search-functionality-nuxt-app-algolia-instantsearch/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/search-functionality-nuxt-app-algolia-instantsearch/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many websites have some sort of search feature because it helps users navigate through their content easily. Implementing it the right way can be tricky and might not give a good user experience. In this tutorial, we will be integrating Algolia, a popular and powerful search service for the best experience on our Nuxt site.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Miracle Onyenma)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility Best Practices for Mobile App Development]]></title>
        <id>611b08a4e884de075217ff23</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mobile-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-30T21:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States Census Bureau estimates that more than 12% of the United States' population is living with a disability. Disabilities can include vision difficulties, hearing difficulties, mobility challenges, and much more.  And a person can become disabled at any stage of their life.  Since a significant portion of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating the Perfect Commit in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352475</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-the-perfect-commit-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-30T14:29:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A commit can be something that helps us stay on top of things. It can be a container for related changes that belong to one and only one topic, and thereby make it easier for us to understand what happened.
In this post, we’re talking about what it takes to produce the "perfect" commit.
The post Creating the Perfect Commit in Git appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tobias Günther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comparing HTML Preprocessor Features]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=350620</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/comparing-html-preprocessor-features/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-30T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
Of the languages that browsers speak, I’d wager that the very first one that developers decided needed some additional processing was HTML. Every single CMS in the world (aside from intentionally headless-only CMSs) …
The post Comparing HTML Preprocessor Features appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Time Of Transition (October 2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-30T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get your desktop ready for fall and the upcoming Halloween season with a fresh batch of desktop wallpapers. Created with love by designers and artists from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for October 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Streams Everywhere (and Fetch for Node.js)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352723</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/web-streams-everywhere-and-fetch-for-node-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T14:51:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome developer advocate Jake Archibald called 2016 “the year of web streams.” Clearly, his prediction was somewhat premature. The Streams Standard was announced back in 2014. It’s taken a while, but there’s now a consistent streaming API implemented …
The post Web Streams Everywhere (and Fetch for Node.js) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ollie Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Front-End Dev Shortcuts in iOS 15]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352627</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/front-end-dev-shortcuts-in-ios-15/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T14:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was pretty stoked when Chris shared a way to “View Source” on mobile. Sure, it’s not the same as a built-in feature but it allows iOS users like myself a way to peek at a site’s code the …
The post Front-End Dev Shortcuts in iOS 15 appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Modern Image Formats: AVIF And WebP]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/modern-image-formats-avif-webp/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/modern-image-formats-avif-webp/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T08:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll highlight how modern image formats (AVIF or WebP) can improve compression by up to 50% and deliver better quality per-byte while still looking visually appealing. We’ll compare what’s possible at high-quality, low-quality and file-size targets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So many little design helper sites!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352669</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/so-many-little-design-helper-sites/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T21:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had one of those little single-serving designer helper sites bookmarked the other day: getwaves.io. Randomized SVG waves! Lots of cool options! Easy to customize! Easy to copy and paste! Well played, z creative labs. 

But then I …
The post So many little design helper sites! appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Accessibility Of Your Markdown]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/improving-accessibility-of-markdown/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/improving-accessibility-of-markdown/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can find Markdown in many places on the Internet. This article covers different aspects of Markdown and how it interacts with other technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Dive Into Cypress For End-to-End Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/cypress-end-to-end-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/cypress-end-to-end-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is end-to-end testing a painful topic for you? In this article, Ramona Schwering explains how to handle end-to-end testing with Cypress and make it make it not so tedious and expensive for yourself, but fun instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ramona Schwering)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.2"/>
        <updated>2021-09-26T18:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: unicode characters in URL caused download error
Fixed: project root npm install error
Added: unit test library
Chore: Dependency updates
Thank you: @CaptNo1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rebuilding A Large E-Commerce Website With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/lessons-learned-ecommerce-nextjs-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/lessons-learned-ecommerce-nextjs-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We made the switch from a more traditional integrated e-commerce platform to a headless platform with Next.js. Here are the most important lessons learned while rebuilding a large e-commerce site with Next.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jonne Kats)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Online Workshop: Frustrating Design Patterns And How To Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/smashing-workshop-frustrating-design-patterns/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/smashing-workshop-frustrating-design-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T06:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve seen them before. Confusing and frustrating design patterns that seem to be chasing you everywhere you go, from one website to another. It’s time to fix them for good in a [free Smashing online workshop](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/workshops/vitaly-friedman-frustrating-patterns/) next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplifying Form Styles With `accent-color`]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/simplifying-form-styles-accent-color/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/simplifying-form-styles-accent-color/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new CSS `accent-color` property makes it quick and easy to roll out our brand colors to certain form inputs by leveraging user agent styles. In this article we’ll take a look at what it does and how to use it alongside `color-scheme` for simple, accessible checkboxes and radio buttons — and imagine how we might use it in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Your `head` Straight: A New CSS Performance Diagnostics Snippet]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/css-head-tag/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/css-head-tag/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We love little useful tools and techniques to help folks get their work done better and faster. Today, we’d love to shine the spotlights on a little helper that helps spot common performance bottlenecks easily: [ct.css](https://csswizardry.com/ct/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build Your Own Mouseless Development Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/mouseless-development-environment/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/mouseless-development-environment/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a development environment with the shell as a keystone offers multiple benefits. You can customize everything depending on your own needs, and the biggest of all, you can control your entire development environment with your keyboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthieu Cneude)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Web Development Tools Are Helping Users Keep Pace With Rapid Change]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-development-tools-users-keep-pace-rapid-change/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-development-tools-users-keep-pace-rapid-change/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last 18 months have been a time of unprecedented turbulence. As the people of the world have flooded online, businesses have joined them, using web development tools to adapt in real-time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Imposter Domains Re-Publishing Your Website?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/imposter-domains-republishing-website/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/imposter-domains-republishing-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content scraping is a fact of life on the Internet. When you think of web scraping, you probably do not think about the scrapers turning around and immediately serving your entire, whole page content on another website. But what if your site content is being re-published?  It might be already happening.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ken Harker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monetize Open-Source Software With Gatsby Functions And Stripe]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/monetize-open-source-software-gatsby-functions-stripe/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/monetize-open-source-software-gatsby-functions-stripe/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Functions provide front-end developers a way to write and use server-side code without the hassle of maintaining a server. If making money from open-source is of interest to you and your site isn’t built using Gatsby, this approach may well be the answer you were looking for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Quality Assurance: From User Requirements To Web Risk Management]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/journey-into-web-quality-assurance/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/journey-into-web-quality-assurance/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twenty years ago, Elie Sloïm chose to dedicate his professional life to web quality assurance. He started asking, ”What does quality mean for a web user?” Well, this article explains everything he has learned along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Elie Sloïm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reasons To Build A CRM-Powered Website For Your Business]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reasons-build-crm-powered-website-business/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reasons-build-crm-powered-website-business/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating a CRM with your business website has numerous benefits. In this article, Zara Cooper explains what these benefits are and why websites should be integrated with a CRM platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.1"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T06:39:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Unexpected nested element in author field crashes the parser
Thank you @ad-m]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing The Need For Pseudo-Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reducing-need-pseudo-elements/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reducing-need-pseudo-elements/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, pseudo-elements have faithfully helped front-end developers implement creative designs. While they still have an important place, we can now leave pseudo-elements behind in some scenarios, thanks to newer CSS properties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcel Moreau)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Power Of Pen And Paper Sketching]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/power-pen-paper-sketching/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/power-pen-paper-sketching/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing for digital spaces, it’s natural to default to digital mockup tools, but doing so cuts out a world of possibilities. Analog drawing can unleash your imagination and allow you to focus on what’s most important at the start: the ideas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tracy Osborn)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orchestrating Complexity With Web Animations API]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/orchestrating-complexity-web-animations-api/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/orchestrating-complexity-web-animations-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are way too many options in Web Animations API to pick them up that easily. Learning how timing works and how to control the playback of several animations at once makes for a solid foundation on which to base your projects on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kirill Myshkin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: Excellent Editorial]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-design-done-well-excellent-editorial/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-design-done-well-excellent-editorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They say content is king, and they’re right. The web has unlocked untold possibilities for storytellers — provided the story is right, of course. Here are some of our favorite examples of editorial content thriving in the digital realm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using SWR React Hooks With Next.js’ Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/useswr-react-hook-library-incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/useswr-react-hook-library-incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When paired with ISR and Next.js’ API routes, SWR can be used to create a responsive user experience. In this article, Sam Poder explains what SWR is, where to use it (and where not), and how to build a website by using Incremental Static Regeneration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sam Poder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Decisions For Building Flexible Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/developer-decisions-building-flexible-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/developer-decisions-building-flexible-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll walk through the process of taking a seemingly simple design for a text-and-media component and deciding how best to translate it into code, keeping in mind the needs of both users and content authors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Smashing Online Workshops on Front-End & UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/new-smashing-online-workshops-sep-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/new-smashing-online-workshops-sep-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the state of HTML Email, Vue.js and Next.js? What are new, smart interface design patterns we could use? Let’s figure it out. With our brand new online workshops on front-end & design. Now with **free workshops** for you to test the waters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New With DevTools: Cross-Browser Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/devtools-cross-browser-edition/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/devtools-cross-browser-edition/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what’s new with developer tools in Firefox, Edge, Chrome and Safari. Discover new and powerful features that will help you be more comfortable and productive when testing and debugging across browsers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Patrick Brosset)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>